骑士！骑士！
Horsemen! Horsemen!
骑士！骑士！骑士！骑士！
Horsemen! Horsemen! Horsemen! Horsemen!
你该不会真以为……我们把你丢下了吧？
Did you think we abandoned you?
还是说，你觉得我们的魔术已经玩不出新花样了？
Or that we'd run out of magic?
那么，女士们先生们，再想想吧，
Well, think again, ladies and gentlemen,
因为好戏 这才刚要开场
because you are about to be amazed.
既然此刻你人在这儿，就说明你
If you're here right now, then you have
破解了谜题，跟上了线索
followed the clues and cracked the code.
恭喜你，欢迎入局
Congratulations, and welcome.
距离骑士上次现身，已经过去了十年，
It's been 10 years since the horseman last appeared,
但我们回来了！
but we are back!
好了，来，靠近点   嗯，再近一点
Okay, so, come in close. Mm, closer.
因为你以为看到的越多，
Because the more you think you see,
就越容易将老把戏重新包装
the easier it will be to dress up old tricks
并骗你以为是新的
and fool you that they are new.
那么，我叫 J·丹尼尔·阿特拉斯，
So, my name is J. Daniel Atlas,
请允许我像往常一样发言，
and allow me to speak as I often do
为我那些不那么有魅力的同事们，我想说...
for my less charismatic colleagues when I say...
呼！回来真好！
Whoo! It is very good to be back!
没错   没错   我们是消失了一阵子，
Yes. Yes. We vanished for a while,
但在魔法的世界里，
but in the world of magic,
所有消失的，终将重现
everything that disappears, reappears.
不过，至少戏法要是变得够漂亮才行
Well, at least if the trick is done right.
我是梅里特·麦金尼
I'm Merritt McKinney.
不像我这位，呃，铁哥们儿丹尼，
Unlike my, uh, very good buddy here, Danny,
今晚在座的各位，大多都把那份自大留在门外了
most of you checked your egos at the door tonight.
你们竟然找到了这个小众的地下集会
You found this little underground soiree
因为你们就是想被耍一回
because you wanted to get fooled.
嘿，大家好   我是杰克·怀尔德
Hey, everyone. I'm Jack Wilder.
战争、疫情、气候变化、人工智能
Wars, pandemics, climate change, AI.
说实话，我们比以往任何时候都更需要魔法
Let's face it, we all need magic more than ever.
所以我要你们非常仔细地观察
So I want you to pay very close attention.
接下来的这场好戏，你们可千万别眨眼
You are not gonna want to miss this next trick.
亨莉·里夫斯，现在是亨莉·里夫斯·斯坦利了
Henley Reeves, now Henley Reeves Stanley.
三个孩子，两只狗，还有一个硕士学位
Three kids, two dogs and a master's degree.
好久不见
It's been a while.
想我们了吗？
Did you miss us?
那些家伙当年可真了不起
Those guys were great back in the day.
我曾经想成为一名魔术师
I used to want to be a magician.
然后我到了12岁
And then I turned 12.
当心点，隔墙有耳
Careful, they might be listening.
哦，我吓得连我身上这件AllSaints外套都在抖呢
Ooh, I'm shaking in my AllSaints.
他们能怎么样？
What are they gonna do?
那是真金吗？
Is that real gold?
什么？ 那是真金吗？
What? Is that real gold?
是啊，我很有钱
Yeah, I'm rich.
伙计，这是魔术表演
This is a magic show, dude.
这里的每个傻瓜都是扒手，
Every fool here is a pickpocket,
或是扒手手里的傻瓜
or a pickpocket's fool.
刚才那是俳句吗？什么意思？
Was that a haiku? What was that?
你们每个人都刚刚收到一张扑克牌
Each of you just received a playing card.
如果你们不介意，呃，把它拿出来好吗？
If you wouldn't mind, uh, pulling it out?
好   现在，我们要洗牌了，
Right. Now, we're gonna shuffle the deck,
所以每个人找到身边的一个随机的人
so everybody find a random person near them
和他们交换牌
and switch cards with them.
等你们交换完之后，
And then when you've done that,
再找另一个人和他交换
find somebody else and switch with them.
好了，很好   呃，现在...
Okay, great. Uh, now...
呃，哒哒哒哒哒... 那边的那位，下面的那位
Uh, duhduhduhduhduh... You there, down there.
我吗？ 对   你的牌是什么？
Me? Yeah. What is your card?
方块A    方块A   好的
Ace of diamonds. Ace of diamonds. Okay.
我们让事情变得更有趣一点
Let's make things a little more complicated here.
这里有谁还有方块A吗？
Does anybody else here have the ace of diamonds?
等等，是我   方块A！
Wait, it's me. Ace of diamonds!
哦！
Ooh!
看来我们有了一个第五骑士，名字不是卢拉
Looks like we have a Fifth Horseman not named Lula.
上台来，你来当我们的助手
Come up on stage, you're gonna be our helper.
动手吧！ 手下2：没错，快动手！
Do it! MAN 2: Yeah, go!
现在，呃，看着我的眼睛
Now, uh, look into my eyes
然后... 睡吧
and... sleep.
宝刀未老
Still got it.
现在，这孩子在你们看来可能很普通，
Now, this might look like an ordinary kid to you,
但今晚，他将像被附身一样表演非凡的魔术
but tonight, he is going to do extraordinary magic
如同被附身的人
like a man possessed.
字面意思
Literally.
亨莉    什么事，梅里特
Henley. Yes, Merritt.
你介意进入他的身体吗？
Would you mind stepping inside his body?
是的   还有，杰克，呃，
Yep. And, Jack, uh,
你为什么不也跳进来呢？
why don't you throw yourself on in there, too?
我最擅长这个了
What I do best.
还有... 哦，上帝保佑你
And... Oh, God help you.
阿特拉斯，你不也滑进来吗？
Atlas, why don't you slither on inside, as well?
我也不妨挤进去
And I might as well wedge myself in there, too.
创造魔法需要一个村庄
It takes a village to make magic.
哦！哇！
Oh! Whoa!
J·丹尼尔·阿特拉斯在此
J. Daniel Atlas in the house.
那么，谁想看魔术？
So, who wants to see a magic trick?
交给你了，梅里特
Take it away, Merritt.
哈喽，你们这些美丽的家伙
Hello, you beautiful people.
大家都知道梅里特·麦金尼会读心术
Now, everyone knows that Merritt McKinney reads minds.
那么现在，我就是他   或者说他是我   谁知道呢？
Well, now, I'm him. Or he's me. Who knows?
呃，我感觉到今晚有人来这里
Uh, I'm sensing someone came here tonight
不是为了享受魔术，而是来搞破坏
not to enjoy magic, but to tear it down.
现场有布雷特·芬尼根吗？
Is there a Brett Finnegan in the house?
什么事？
What up?
现在，你和你的朋友们在这里
Now, you and your friends here
建立了坎普霍巴特加密货币交易所
set up the Camp Hobart Crypto Exchange.
事实   是的   没错    我们就是干这个的
Fact. Yep. Yeah. It's what we're about.
拿走了纽约市的
Took the good people of New York's
雇员退休金和福利基金一半的现金
employee pension and welfare fund half its cash.
呃，你夸大其词了，
Uh, you're rounding up,
而且，风险都明确说明过了
and also, the risks were laid out very clearly.
大家都知道自己要面对什么，伙计
Everybody knew what they were getting into, dude.
你把利润藏在海外了吗？
Did you hide the profits offshore?
账户尾号是
Account ending
53297？
in 53297?
没有我的，呃... 你不可能知道那个
You couldn't know that without my, uh...
哦，这是真金吗？
Oh, is this real gold?
布雷特，你应该更小心
Brett, you ought to be more careful
保管你的东西，伙计
with your things, man.
梅里特是通灵者，但我，杰克，
Merritt's a psychic, but me, Jack,
我擅长手法魔术
I'm into sleight of hand.
问问你的朋友们
Ask your friends.
他们刚刚为缩小贫富差距出了一份力
They've just done their part to close the wealth gap.
什么？搞什么...
What? What the...
现在，来点小再分配
Now, here's a little redistribution.
嘿！嘿，嘿！
Hey! Hey, hey!
谢谢   谢谢
Thank you. Thank you.
你等着吃官司吧，伙计！我会揍扁你！
Lawyer up, dude! I'll kick your ass!
哦哦！
Uhoh!
有人忘了亨莉会飞
Someone forgot Henley can fly.
剩下的交给我们吧，但请大家鼓掌
We can take it from here, but a round of applause
献给台上最棒的骑士
for the best Horseman on stage.
呼！哇
Whoo! Wow.
嘿，嘿，嘿   嘿，嘿
Hey, hey, hey. Hey, hey.
太棒了   那么，大家，拿起你们的饮料，
Fantastic. So, everybody, I want you to take your drink,
把它倒在你们的牌面上
and I want you to pour it onto the face of your card.
能做到吗？
Can you do that?
你们每张牌上的那12个独特的词
Those 12 unique words on each of your cards
是你们新加密货币钱包的密码
form the password to your new crypto wallet.
哦！ 登录
Oh! Log on
你就会发现布雷特偷走的数百万...
and you'll find Brett's stolen millions more...
得到了更公平的重新分配
fairly redistributed.
我的天哪   五... 5万美金！
Oh, my God. Fifty... 50,000 bucks!
5万！
50,000!
你完蛋了，伙计！
You're freaking done, dude!
哇，哇！冷静点，姜饼人，
Whoa, whoa! Cool your head, gingerbread,
因为我有个预感
'cause I am having a vision.
呃，也许警察马上就要破门而入了！
Eh, maybe cops are gonna come bursting through that door!
所以你自己也表演个魔术吧
So perform a magic trick of your own
在三，二，一的倒计时后消失
and disappear in three, two, one.
现在靠近点   嗯，再近一点
Now come in close. Mm, closer.
因为你以为看到的越多，就越容易
Because the more you think you see, the easier it will be
将老把戏重新包装... 什么？
to dress up old tricks... What?
并骗你以为是新的
and fool you that they are new.
哦，我的天哪，不
Oh, my God, no.
不！
No!
《惊天魔盗团3》
本影视由米奇爸爸
基于官方英文字幕翻译制作
听着，在我看来，我觉得你做得很好
Look, in my opinion, I think you did a great job.
呃，我觉得我演阿特拉斯演得不错
Uh, I think my Atlas was good.
我演的梅里特可能还需要改进
My Merritt could probably use some work.
嗯    就像圣地亚哥的瘾君子
Mm. It's like a San Diego stoner
和捕虾船船长生的孩子
and a shrimp boat captain had a baby.
当然
Sure.
不，说真的，博斯科，我不知道你是怎么做到的
No, seriously, Bosco, I don't know how you do it.
好的模仿不仅仅是模仿
A good impersonation isn't just about the mimicry.
它关乎对细节的关注，
It's about attention to detail,
个性和细微差别
personality and nuance.
好吧   好吧   让我试试，让我试试
Okay. Okay. Let me try, let me try.
嗯... 我是 J·丹尼尔·阿特拉斯
Um... I'm J. Daniel Atlas.
你看得越仔细，看到的就越少
The closer you look, the less you see.
还差点意思
It was something.
是的   呃，你多练练
Yep. Uh, you'll work on it.
我演得还行啊    是个好的开始
I wasn't bad. It was a good start.
但还需要改进    好吧，当然
But it could use some work. Okay, sure.
你一直在看什么？ 没什么，没什么，没什么
What do you keep looking at? Nothing, nothing, nothing.
伙计，高兴点   伙计们，打起精神来！看看我们！
Dude, cheer up. Guys, come on! Look at us!
看看我们走了多远   我们今晚大获全胜
Look at how far we've come. We totally scored tonight.
好吧，下次你戴粉红色的假发，好吗？
All right, next time, you wear the pink wig, okay?
不要
No.
伙计，又锁上了    好吧，我来开锁
Dude, it's locked again. Okay, I'll pick it.
等等，等等，等一下   表演一下那个
Wait, wait, wait, hold on. Do the thing.
不要    求你了，表演一下那个
No. Please do the thing.
完全没必要    太酷了
It's so unnecessary. It's so cool.
我来帮你拿包    完全没必要
I'll hold your bag. It's so unnecessary.
来吧，很有趣的    好吧
Come on, it's fun. Okay.
你可以的
You got this.
她像个小马里奥    她确实像马里奥
She's like a little Mario. She is like Mario.
小心，小心   千万别死
Careful, careful. Please don't die.
你还好吗？ 琼：没事
Are you okay? JUNE: Yeah.
如果我会那个，我就只干那个
If I could do that, I would only do that.
太酷了    太疯狂了
It's so cool. It's insane.
满意了？
Happy?
是的，太棒了    是啊
Yeah, that was awesome. Yeah.
请让我们进去   外面冷
Please let us in. It's cold.
呼
Whoo.
整个城市最好的公寓
Best apartment in the whole city.
是的，而且除了我们没人会看到它
Yep, and no one will ever see it but us.
每个人啊…
Everybody...
真是遗憾
It's such a shame.
但在我的盔甲之下 我也是凡人…
But in my armor I am a man...
靠近点
Come in close.
再近一点
Closer.
那家伙死定了
That guy is so screwed.
现在谁有钱了？
Who's rich now?
查理，你能把那东西关了吗，拜托？
Charlie, can you turn that thing off, please?
我想我今晚受够阿特拉斯了
I think I've had enough Atlas for one night.
好的，没问题
Yeah, I got you.
消失，重现
disappears, reappears.
至少如果戏法做对了的话
At least if the trick is done right.
博斯科，你能看看有披萨吗？我好饿
Bosco, can you check for pizza? I'm so hungry.
呃，我也饿
Ugh, me, too.
我们是四骑士！
We are the Four Horsemen!
没有披萨，但有啤酒
No pizza, but we got beer.
而且，真的只有啤酒    靠近点   因为
And, no, literally just beer. Closer. Because
你以为看到的越多... 有人要喝吗？
the more you think you see... Any takers?
是的，给我来一罐
Yeah, I'll have one.
伙计，说真的，把那东西关了
Dude, seriously, turn that thing off.
我关了啊
I did.
好吧   真好笑，伙计们   另一个投影仪在哪？
Okay. Real funny, guys. Where's the other projector?
我不是全息影像
I'm not a hologram.
"我不是全息影像   " 对   是的
"I'm not a hologram." Right. Yes.
全息影像就该这么说
Exactly what a hologram would say.
哦，我的天哪，你是真人    别再碰我的脸了
Oh, my God, you're real. Never touch my face again.
我很抱歉   我以为你是全息影像
I'm so sorry. I thought that you were a hologram.
我绝不会那么做的   我是你的超级粉丝
I would never do that. I'm a huge fan of yours.
你好吗？
How are you?
你是怎么找到我们的？
How did you find us?
我不知道   大概花了30秒
I don't know. Took me about 30 seconds.
如果我能这么轻易找到你们，
And if it was this easy for me to find you,
那警察找你们会有多难？
how hard would it be for the police?
哇，等等，警察？ 是的，警察
Whoa, hold on, the police? Yeah, the police.
警察为什么要找我们？
Why would the police be looking for us?
呃，我不知道，难道是因为
Uh, I don't know, what about that
你们刚刚搞的那场小劫案？
little heist you just pulled?
或者你们非法占用这个地方的事实，
Or the fact that you're squatting in this place
或者你们的电来自
or that your electricity comes from
角落里的那个电闸箱？
the circuit box in the corner?
我不知道，可能性多着呢   我说得对吗，小丑？
I don't know, it could be anything. Am I right, Bozo?
博斯科
Bosco.
嗯    博斯科·勒罗伊
Hmm. Bosco Leroy.
啊，没错，博斯科·勒罗伊
Ah, that's right, yeah, Bosco Leroy.
什么，你是打了，
What, did you type, uh,
"虚构的魔术师名字" 到ChatGPT里吗？
"fictional magician name" into ChatGPT?
不，那真的是我的真名，阿特拉斯
No, that's actually my real name, Atlas.
嗯
Hmm.
什么，你妈妈是和地图睡过觉吗？
What, did your mom have sex with a map?
这不好笑    嗯
That's not funny. Hmm.
你对我们一无所知，伙计
You don't know anything about us, dude.
我对你们了如指掌    哦
I know everything about you. Oh.
名字可疑的博斯科·勒罗伊，
The dubiously named Bosco Leroy,
本应有前途的演艺生涯
a promising acting career
被沉重的学生贷款毁掉了
cut short by crippling student loans.
真遗憾你不得不从茱莉亚学院退学，
It's a bummer you had to drop out of Juilliard,
但你从未停止表演
but you never stopped performing.
呃，如果我没记错，你上一个有报酬的演出，
Uh, if memory serves, your last paid gig,
我想，是在时代广场扮成艾摩吧？
I think, was dressing as Elmo in Times Square?
好吧，首先，我从来没扮过艾摩
Okay, first of all, I was never Elmo.
是红色的天线宝宝
It's the red Teletubby.
小波！
Po!
什么？ 红色的天线宝宝
What? The red Teletubby.
她叫小波    哦，小波！
Her name is Po. Oh, Po!
她是我最喜欢的一个
She's my favorite one.
对吧？
Right?
她叫小波    真可爱
Her name is Po. Cute.
还有你，琼·鲁克莱尔
And you, June Rouclere.
被父母逼着去的每一所寄宿学校都开除了你
Kicked out of every boarding school your parents forced you to attend.
我想，你不太喜欢权威吧
Not a big fan of authority, I take it.
呃，让我猜猜
Uh, let me guess.
呃，你觉得"老家伙们"把地球搞坏了，
Uh, you think the "olds" broke the planet
你们这一代有责任收拾他们的烂摊子
and it's your generation's duty to clean up their mess.
我说得对吗？ 我说错了吗？
Am I right? Am I wrong?
不
No.
所以你就离家出走，
And so, you ran away from home,
一路跑到纽约，在那里遇到了这家伙
made your way to New York, where you ran into this guy
在坦宁魔术商店，查理·盖斯
at Tannin's Magic Shop, Charlie Gayes.
是的，嗨    是啊，嗨
Yeah, hi. Yeah, hi.
嗨    是啊，嗨
我在网上确实找不到太多关于你的信息
I actually couldn't find a lot about you online.
不过，我知道你是个孤儿，
Although, I do know you were an orphan and
整个童年都在寄养家庭进进出出，
you were in and out of foster care your entire childhood,
在你遇到这两个人之前，
and that you didn't know the meaning of family
你都不知道家庭意味着什么
until you hooked up with these two.
所以，你们三个一直
And so, the three of you have been working
在搞你们的小罗宾汉行动，
your little Robin Hood act for years now,
试图一次一个戏法地改变世界，
trying to change the world one trick at a time,
直到现在你们最大胆的盗窃，盗用我的身份
all leading to your riskiest theft to date, my identity.
你当时在场？
You were there?
你把我们的脸贴在了
You had our faces plastered
城里每一个脚手架和地铁站
on every scaffolding and subway stop in the city.
顺便说一句，那是侵犯版权的
That's copyright infringement, by the way.
我当然在场
Of course I was there.
那么，你觉得怎么样？
So, what'd you think?
我觉得你的梅里特需要改进
I think your Merritt needs work.
我就知道    这是个敏感话题
I knew it. That's a sensitive topic.
你根本不明白    不   他在撒谎
You don't even get it. No. He's lying.
但整体设计令人印象深刻
But overall design was impressive.
我猜，你就是那个，安静的家伙？
And that's you, I assume, the quiet guy?
典型的，幕后工作者    是啊，嗯，
Textbook, behind the scenes. Yeah, well,
亚历山大·赫尔曼... 哦，天哪
Alexander Herrmann... Oh, boy.
他说过，为他设计戏法的人
he said that the people who designed his tricks
才是真正的天才
were the real geniuses.
你居然知道那个人的名字，
The fact that you know that man's name,
"幕后工作者"，很明显
"behind the scenes" clearly.
还有你，你的手法魔术很高级   手很灵活
And you, your sleight of hand was advanced. Good dexterity.
你动作迅速敏捷   真的，我印象深刻
You're quick and nimble on your feet. Really, I was impressed.
谢谢    不客气
Thanks. You're welcome.
听起来我们很棒嘛
Sounds like we're pretty great.
你们还差得远呢
You're far from it.
但是，呃，也许稍加改进，你们可以做到
But, uh, maybe with a little fine tuning, you could be.
是的，我... 我能明白为什么天眼派我来找你们
Yeah, I could... I could see why The Eye sent me to you.
抱歉    等等，你说"天眼"？
I'm sorry. Wait, did you say "The Eye"?
是的，天眼
Yeah, The Eye.
好了，听着
All right, listen.
三周前，这张卡片寄到了我的公寓，
This card arrived at my apartment three weeks ago,
连同四张机票
along with four plane tickets
还有隐藏在夹层里的指示，
and instructions hidden in the lining
是一个比你们所见过的任何戏法
for a trick bigger and better
都要宏大、都要精彩的戏法
than anything you have ever seen.
一个出于某种原因，包含了你们三人的戏法
A trick that, for some reason, includes the three of you.
我们？ 嗯
Us? Mmhmm.
为什么不是其他骑士？ 不，
Why not the other Horsemen? No,
其他骑士已经死了    什么？
the other horsemen are dead. What?
对我来说，他们对我而言死了   别插嘴
To me, they're dead to me. Stop interrupting.
不，事情变得很情绪化   大家都退出了
No, things got emotional. Everyone quit.
我去澳大利亚徒步旅行了   说来话长
I took a walkabout in Australia. It's a long story.
所以现在你需要我们？
And now you need us?
根据那张卡片，是的
According to that card, yes.
好吧，我们不需要你，所以...
Well, we don't need you, so...
博斯科
Bosco.
什么？我们需要他干什么？我们现在很成功
What? What do we need this guy for? We're crushing it.
你们很成功？你们只是从
You're crushing it? You're stealing
一些加密货币佬那里偷了点小钱
a little money from some crypto bro.
我说的是大鱼，伙计
I'm talking about big fish here, man.
我指的是那些会
I'm talking about something that will
真正产生影响的事情
make a real difference.
我以为这就是你们这些年轻人追求的
I thought that's what you kids are all about.
是的   不，完全正确
It is. No, exactly.
是的，我们是
Yes, we are.
但是我觉得我们可以自己抓鱼
Yeah, but I think we can catch our own fish.
你们能吗？ 不，不，他...
You can? No, no, he...
祝你们好运    什么？不
Good luck with that. What? No.
你能等一秒钟吗？
Can you just wait one second?
你在干什么？发生... 发生什么事了？
What are you doing? What's... what's going on?
你疯了吗？
Are you out of your mind?
这是 J·丹尼尔·阿特拉斯    是的，我知道他是谁
This is J. Daniel Atlas. Yeah, I know who he is.
他是个传奇人物
He's a freaking legend.
他曾经是传奇   现在他有点混蛋
He was a legend. Now he's just kind of a dick.
你能... 是的，当然
Can you... Yeah, sure.
博斯科，他是有点混蛋，但他是骑士之一
Bosco, he's kind of a dick, but he is a Horseman.
我的意思是，拜托，就相信我们这一次，求你了
I mean, come on, just trust us on this, please.
好吧   做决定的时候到了，孩子们   你们打算怎么办？
Okay. Decision time, kids. What's it gonna be?
你们加入...
Are you in...
还是不加入？
or are you out?
戏法是什么？
What's the trick?
欢迎，尊敬的社区成员们，
Welcome, esteemed community members,
宝贵的媒体，朋友们和同事们
valued press, friends and colleagues.
我们今晚齐聚一堂是为了庆祝
We are gathered here tonight to celebrate.
范德堡最新最伟大的矿场，
Vanderberg's latest and greatest mine,
C3，或者我们喜欢称呼它为，
C3, or as we like to call her,
"Amahle"，祖鲁语意为"美丽的那一个"
"Amahle," Zulu for "The Beautiful One."
因为在母亲的眼里，
Because every child is beautiful
每个孩子都是美丽的
in the eyes of its mother.
我们的客户可以放心，
Our customer can rest assured
当他们购买这世界上最伟大的爱情象征时，
that when they buy the world's greatest symbol of love
它是在纯粹的爱的过程中产生的
that it was produced with nothing but.
为Amahle，也为你们所有人干杯
To Amahle, and to all of you.
非常感谢大家远道而来
Well, thank you all so much for making the trip out here.
我想你们都对Amahle印象深刻
Now, I take it you were all impressed by Amahle.
抱歉，是C3
Sorry, C3.
哦，相当壮观   是的，太神奇了
Oh, it's quite dramatic. Yeah, it's amazing.
但我理解你们选择在这个美好的日子
But I also understand that you have chosen
提出一些关切，
this fine day to broach some concerns,
这与你们的预期相反，我并不介意
which, contrary to your expectations, I don't begrudge.
尽管问吧
Fire away.
好的   呃，董事会认为
Right. Well, um, the board feels that
预测可能过于乐观...
projections might be optimistic...
嗯
Mm.
考虑到实验室培育钻石的竞争加剧，
with increasing competition from lab grown
以及，万一借贷利率大...
and, in the event borrowing rates plum...
威廉   威廉
William. William.
我父亲很爱你，但有
My father loved you, but there was
个理由他称你为他的乌云
a reason he called you his dark cloud.
真遗憾
Aw, shame.
范德堡家族从不失败
The Vanderberg family does not lose.
正如你们所知，我们的赛车团队刚刚
As you're well aware, our motorsports team just won
第七次赢得摩纳哥锦标赛
the Monaco Championship for the seventh time.
这个矿场会产出的
The mine will produce.
下一个？
Next?
好的
Right.
定价   你为...设定的最低价格
Pricing. The minimums that you've set for...
威廉，你能迁就我一下吗？
Will you humor me, William?
做一个关于现实的演示？
In a demonstration about reality?
这颗钻石，大概，多少，55克拉？
This diamond is say, what, 55 carats?
世界钻石中心会定价为300万美元
The AWDC would price it at 3,000,000 US dollars.
威廉，你能张开嘴
William, will you open your mouth
伸出舌头吗？
and stick out your tongue?
现在
Now.
真的吗？ 真的
Really? Really.
现在，如果威廉吞下它，
Now, if William here were to swallow it,
这颗完全相同的钻石会撕碎他的喉咙
that selfsame diamond would tear his throat to shreds.
他会在救护车到达前失血而死
He would bleed to death before paramedics arrived.
所以，对世界钻石中心来说，是300万，
So, to the AWDC, it's 3,000,000,
但对威廉来说，是无价之宝
but to William, priceless.
那么告诉我，作为负责
Tell me then, as the CEO responsible
世界上最后几个伟大钻石矿的CEO，
for the world's last great diamond mines,
我应该削减我们的利润，
should I undercut our profits,
还是应该选择我清楚的
or should I choose prices
我们独特的客户愿意支付的价格？
that I know our unique clients will pay?
如我所料
As I thought.
现在...
Now...
除非还有更多问题，
unless there are more concerns,
我想带着我的价目表去安特卫普
I would like to head to Antwerp with my price list
展示我们的钻石了
and show off our stones.
哦，呃，你知道，你本可以
Oh, uh, you know, you probably could have led
用免费的欧洲之旅当开场白？
with a free trip to Europe?
你知道，关于安特卫普一个鲜为人知的事实是...
You know, a little known fact about Antwerp is that...
哦，太好了，更多魔术冷知识   真有趣
Oh, great, more magic trivia. This is fun.
不，我只是想说
No, I was just gonna say that
他们做的饼干很好吃
they make great biscuits.
哦，真的吗？我们真的能吃点吗，拜托？
Oh, do they? Can we actually get some, please?
当然，阿特拉斯请客   不
On Atlas, obviously. No.
不，不，我不会给你们买饼干的
No, no, I'm not getting you biscuits.
我刚给你们买了巧克力，好吗？
I just got you chocolates, okay?
好了，听着，这不是度假，好吗？
All right, listen, this is not a vacation, okay?
我们只有三天时间来准备一个魔术效果，
We have three days to prepare an effect
一个会让你们那勉强及格的佩珀尔幻象魔术
that'll make your barely passable Pepper's Ghost trick
看起来像洞穴壁画一样的魔术
look like a cave painting.
好了，过来
All right, come here.
心之钻石，历史上最珍贵的宝石，
The Heart Diamond, the most valuable jewel in history
以及范德堡矿业公司的基石
and the foundation of the Vanderberg Mining Corporation.
多年来，这个家族一直把这块大石头藏在
Now, for years, the family's kept this big rock
他们秘密的地下金库里，
hidden inside their secret vault,
地下70层
70 stories underground.
而且不是随便的地下，是阿拉伯沙漠
And not just any ground. The Arabian Desert.
除了他们最信任的团队，没有人进去过
No one beyond their most trusted team has been inside.
通过一台唯一的电梯进入，
Access through a single elevator,
由武装警卫持续监控...
constantly monitored by armed guards...
身份已核实
Identity verified.
并且在一个多层次的
and behind a multilevel
生物识别安全系统之后
biometric security system.
但全世界都会关注，
But the world will be watching,
因为半个世纪以来第一次，
because for the first time in half a century,
那颗钻石将被运到这里
that diamond is being traveled here
到安特卫普，以建立信誉，
to Antwerp, to establish credibility
并在三天后的一场私人拍卖中
and to spur bidding at a private auction
为公司的最新发现激起竞价
for the company's latest finds in three days' time.
好了，显然，我支持偷窃
Okay, obviously, I'm down for stealing.
但这颗钻石有什么特别的？
But what makes this diamond so special?
嗯，因为神秘的塔罗牌让我们这么做的，琼，对吧？
Well, because the magical tarot card told us to, June, right?
是的，好吧，说得真可爱   但能让我说完吗？
Yeah, okay, that's very cute. But can I please finish?
你还没说完？天哪，你讲了半天了
You're not finished? Jeez, you've been talking forever.
是的，我还要接着讲
Yes, and I'm about to talk more.
所以，请，注意听
So, please, pay attention.
几十年来，先是彼得·范德堡，
For decades, first, Peter Vanderberg,
现在是他女儿，维罗妮卡，
now his daughter, Veronika,
一直在以虚高的价格把这些钻石卖给
have been selling these diamonds at inflated prices
全世界的军火商、人贩子、军阀，
to arms dealers, traffickers, warlords the world over,
来，比如说，帮他们洗钱
to, like, help launder their money.
所以，我是说，这些钱是脏钱
So, I mean, the cash is dirty.
我是说，有些情况下，上面真的沾满了鲜血
I mean, in some cases, it's, like, literally bloodsoaked.
但是然后，瞧...
But then, voila...
通过交换这些珍贵的宝石，钱就被洗干净了
it's cleaned in exchange for these precious stones.
她让世界上所有最坏的人成为可能
She makes all the world's worst people possible.
所以，寄出那张塔罗牌的人...
So, whoever sent that tarot card...
是这个世界上仅存的少数真正正直的人
Are the few truly honorable people left in this world.
唯一还关心正义的人
The only people that still care about justice.
是我很久没联系过的人
They're people I haven't spoken to in a long time.
他们自称"天眼"，
They call themselves "The Eye,"
他们想让我们做一件骑士们从未做到的事
and they want us to do something that the Horsemen never could.
这个，伙计，
This, man,
这是一个机会，将一根木桩
this is a chance to drive a stake
钉入女恶魔自己的心脏
through the heart of the devil herself.
我们干吧
Let's do it.
今晚拍卖会上所有的目光都会聚焦在我
All eyes will be on me
和心形钻石上
and the Heart tonight at the auction.
我必须看起来光彩照人
I have to look dazzling.
你有那种小猫之吻的颜色吗？
Do you have that Kitten Kiss color?
莱塔博
Lethabo.
什么事？ 吸管
Yes? Straw.
那个来自《名利场》的英国摄影师叫什么名字？
Who's that British photographer from Vanity Fair?
呃，他叫什么来着？马克...
Uh, what's his name again? Marc...
马克·史克里伯？
Marc Scriber?
施赖伯，我的天    施赖伯
Schreiber, good God. Schreiber.
确认他，取消其他人
Confirm him, cancel the others.
我们去年覆盖面广   今年，走精品路线
We went wide last year. This year, exclusivity.
好的    我们是开放的，透明的
All right. We're open, transparent.
我们没什么可隐瞒的
We have nothing to hide.
好的，完美   我会办妥的
Okay, perfect. I'll have it done.
我是维罗妮卡
This is Veronika.
嘘 小宝贝
Hush little baby
你是谁？
Who is this?
安静别出声
Don't say a word
爸爸会给你买只知更鸟
Papa's gonna buy you a mocking bird
清场
Vacate.
要是那知更鸟
And if that mocking bird
你怎么弄到这个号码的？
How did you get this number?
不唱歌
Don't sing
爸爸会给你买枚钻石戒指
Papa's gonna buy you a diamond ring
这是私人线路，而且这有点不合时宜
This is a private line, and that was a bit tone deaf.
我问你是谁
I asked who you are.
啊，维罗妮卡
Ah, Veronika.
你左边的储物柜
The storage unit to your left.
看起来很眼熟？
Look familiar?
它属于15年前死去的那个男孩
It belonged to that boy who died 15 years ago.
这对我或任何人都毫无意义
This means nothing to me or anyone.
真的吗？
Really?
你我都知道你做了什么
You and I both know what you did.
听着，如果你有真凭实据
Look, if you have real evidence
并且想抓我，为什么不直接用呢？
and you're out to get me, why not just use it?
十五年前，你夺走了你父亲的最爱
Fifteen years ago, you took what your father loved most.
现在我要对你做同样的事
Now I'm going to do the same to you.
我想要心之钻石
I want the Heart Diamond.
你会把它给我
You're going to give it to me.
否则我就要举起一面镜子，
Or I'm going to hold up a looking glass
让全世界看清你的真面目
for the whole world to see you as you are.
来吧   我没什么可隐瞒的
Go ahead. I have nothing to hide.
哦，我的天哪    嘿
Oh, my God. Hey.
我真的很抱歉
I'm so sorry about that.
你好   你能帮我找到这个吗？
Hi. Can you help me find this?
我找了整整一个小时了
I've been looking literally for an hour.
是的   就在那边，女士
Yes. It's gonna be right over there, ma'am.
马克·施赖伯，詹姆斯·温，范德堡公关
Marc Schreiber, James Winn, Vanderberg PR.
非常欣赏您的作品
Huge admirer of your work.
詹姆斯？丹妮怎么了？
James? What happened to Dani?
哦，丹妮   是的，很遗憾，我们不得不让她走
Oh, Dani. Yeah, sadly, we had to let her go.
原来她是种族主义者
Turns out she was racist.
而且，她把你订在了雷迪森布鲁酒店
And also, she booked you into the Radisson Blu
一个部分海景的双人间
in a partial view, double. Ugh.
幸运的是，我自作主张把你换到了FRANQ酒店
Thankfully, I took the liberty of moving you to the FRANQ.
我确实喜欢FRANQ
I do love the FRANQ.
是的，总统套房才配得上，嗯，
Yes, the presidential suite is befitting of, well,
总统和像您这样有才华的摄影师
presidents and talented photographers like yourself.
呃，您的晚宴邀请已经改道发送了
Uh, your gala invitation has been rerouted.
如果我能核对一下您的确认信息？
If I could just check your confirmation?
谢谢
Thank you.
我也把您的拍摄时间从晚上7点改到了9点，
I also bumped your shoot from 7:00 to 9:00 p.m.
让您有足够的时间施展魔法
to give you proper time to make your magic.
有人懂行    是的
Someone gets it. Yeah.
我如超新星般闪耀
I'm shinin' like a supernova
高举双手 敞开心扉…
With my hands up high And my heart wide open...
我如钻石般更加璀璨
I shine even more bright Like a diamond
将恐惧从肩头拂去…
Brush that fear right off my shoulder...
以实验室培育的钻石为例
Take, for instance, diamonds created in laboratories.
它们声称有价值，
They purport to have value,
但它们既不天然也不稀有
but they're neither natural nor rare.
诚实的女人谁会想要一枚假货戴在手指上？
What honest woman wants a falsehood on her finger?
我同意
I agree.
自然宝石背后蕴藏的力量，
One of the great truths left
是尚存的伟大真理之一
is the power behind a natural gem.
真正的钻石让人充满激情，
Real diamonds fill people with passion,
几个世纪以来一直如此
as they have for centuries.
没错   事实上，玛丽·安托瓦内特，
That's right. In fact, MarieAntoinette,
只戴了一天希望钻石，
wore the Hope Diamond for a single day,
一个月后...
and a month later...
就被一些非常，嗯，如你所说，充满激情的人们
was dragged to the guillotine
拖上了断头台
by some very, well, as you say, passionate folks.
玛丽·安托瓦内特不是因钻石而死
MarieAntoinette didn't die because of a diamond.
她是死于令人发指的缺乏同理心
She died because of a monstrous lack of empathy.
嗯...
Well...
事实是，她从未戴过希望钻石
And truth is, she never even wore the Hope.
只是人们相信她戴过
People just believe she did.
真的吗？这有点意思
Really? That's kind of interesting.
所以杀死她的不是暴民，
So it was not the mob that killed her,
也不是断头台，
and it was not the guillotine,
而是一个... 一个故事
it was a... a story.
我一定不知道我自己的宾客名单
I must not know my own guest list.
您是做钻石生意的吗？
Are you in the diamond business?
不，不，我和你一样，是做幻觉生意的
No, no, I'm in the illusion business, like you.
看，几个世纪以来，钻石一文不值，
See, for centuries, diamonds were worthless
直到一些非常聪明、非常富有的人，
until some very smart, very rich people
像这里的维罗妮卡，告诉我们，不仅
like Veronika here, told us that, not only
这些玻璃碎片是稀有的，
are these little shards of glass rare,
而且没有自尊的情侣
but that no selfrespecting couple
可以不用钻石而结婚
could possibly get married without one.
不，现在，那才是一个好的魔术戏法
No, now, that one is a good magic trick.
这个戏法的问题是，嗯...
The problem with the trick is, um...
所有好的戏法都有个小转折
All the good ones have a little twist in the tale.
是你吗？
Is it you?
什么是我？
Is what me?
当然不是    不，不
Of course not. No, no.
我的意思是，如果我没有展示
I mean, you wouldn't have let me in had I not demonstrated
最优良的道德品质，像你的一些其他客人一样
the finest moral fiber, like some of your other guests.
我注意到那边是军火商路易斯·布里塞尼奥
I notice Luis Briseño, the arms dealer over there.
您好，先生
Hello, sir.
当然还有玛丽亚·博尔特尼克，当她明星光环笼罩时，
And of course, Maria Bortnick, when starstruck,
如何在社交的同时还能垄断她的国家媒体
how she manages to mingle while monopolizing her state media.
或许您愿意表明身份
Perhaps you'd care to reveal yourself.
那样我们就能用同样的标准来审视您了
Then we can apply the same scrutiny to you.
嗯
Hmm.
暂时还不行
Not just yet.
抱歉打扰了
I'm sorry for interrupting.
不必了
That won't be necessary.
让她吃蛋糕吧
Let him eat cake.
马克·施赖伯
Marc Schreiber.
维罗妮卡·范德伯格
Veronika Vanderberg.
我们速战速决，好吗？
Let's make this quick, shall we?
我们的拍卖会马上开始
Our auction begins shortly.
我相信您能拍出我和心形钻石的风采
I trust you can do me and the Heart justice.
是的   我只有一个原则   我说了算
Yes. I only have one rule. What I say goes.
嗯，我相信我能找到我顺从的一面
Well, I'm sure I can find my submissive side.
嗯，如果找不到，我会帮你找到
Well, if not, I'll find it for you.
哦   我喜欢你
Ooh. I like you.
这边请，亲爱的
Right this way, darling.
我不想太哑光    当然   当然，当然
I don't want to be too matte. Sure. Sure, sure.
我也不喜欢我鼻子两侧反光
And I don't like the sides of my nose shining.
好的
Okay.
给我看看    嗯
Show me. Mmhmm.
打扰一下，能请我镜头里的小苍蝇
Excuse me, can the little fruit fly
飞走，飞走，飞走吗？
in my shot please shoo, shoo, shoo?
谢谢
Thank you.
比那颗钻石更宝贵的是我的时间
The only thing more valuable than that diamond is my time.
我研究过你
I did my research on you.
你的行业，和我的行业一样，
Your industry, like mine,
都被制造商传说所困扰
is besieged by manufacturer lore.
但您，您向我们展现了美本来的样子
But you, you bring us beauty as it is.
在这一点上我们很像
We're alike in that regard.
我们不卖虚假，我们卖现实
We don't sell contrivance, we sell reality.
嗯，我想说我们根本不卖
Well, I would argue that we don't sell at all.
是别人买
Others buy.
嗯
Hmm.
让我看看...
Let's see...
呃... 把钻石拿出来
Uh... The diamond, take it out.
不，小子
Nah, boy.
绝对不行
Absolutely not.
玻璃反光会破坏照片
The glare in the glass will mar the photos.
我无法容忍瑕疵
I don't tolerate imperfections.
我想像范德堡女士这样迷人的女士也不会容忍
I don't imagine someone as ravishing as Ms. Vanderberg does either.
所以，要么拿出来，要么另请高明
So, take it out or find yourself a new photographer.
说实话，我正希望你开口呢
In truth, I was hoping you'd ask.
我不记得问过你
I don't remember asking.
它在那儿
There it is.
太美了   开始吧   太棒了
Beautiful. Work it. Fabulous.
太棒了    太棒了    太棒了
Fabulous.  Fabulous.  Fabulous.
太美了
Beautiful.
是的   微笑，我们很开心
Yes. Smiling, we're having fun.
这正是我们想要的
This is what we came for.
稳住，稳住
Hold it, hold it.
就是这张完美照片
That's the money shot.
稳住
Hold it.
而你，女士，离得够远了
And you, ma'am, are far enough.
我只是想... 我想帮忙
I'm just trying... I'm trying to help.
她的额头比钻石还闪
Her forehead is shinier than the diamond.
事实上，我在做我的工作   我不听你指挥
Actually, I'm doing my job. I don't take orders from you.
关于心形钻石的事，你得听我的
When it comes to the Heart, you listen to me.
出去    我... 我自己能走
Get out. I... I can walk myself.
谢谢    好的
Thank you. Right.
施赖伯先生
Mr. Schreiber.
如果您真如您所言那般出色，
If you're all you purport to be,
您现在应该已经拍到您需要的了
you should already have what you need.
足够了   谢谢您    太好了
More than enough. Thank you. Excellent.
嗯，很愉快，但我有买家在等着
Well, it's been a pleasure, but I have buyers waiting.
我已经受够这些胡闹了
I've had enough of this of this nonsense.
确保把它保管好
Make sure it's secured.
好的，莱塔博
Yes, Lethabo.
搞什么，发生什么事了？ 我不知道   我不知道
What the hell, what happened? I don't know. I don't know.
时间紧迫   我们走
Time's ticking. Let's go.
终于，我们期待已久的拍卖会开始了
At last, the auction we've all been waiting for.
现在，如果你们今晚在这里，
Now, if you're here tonight,
你们可能以为自己什么都见过了
you probably think you've seen everything.
所以我要问你们...
So it is to you that I ask...
一切吗？
Everything?
它已有四分之一世纪未曾公开露面
It's not been seen in person for a quarter of a century.
依然是迄今为止发现的最大钻石，心形钻石
Still the largest diamond ever discovered, the Heart.
恭喜你们所有人，
Congratulations to all of you
以及你们逍遥法外这么久
and for getting away with it for so long.
那么猜猜怎么着？
Well, guess what?
气候变化
Climate change
也不相信你们
doesn't believe in you, either.
你们从我们的地球母亲那里攫取财富，
You tore your fortunes from our Mother Earth,
乘坐私人飞机烧毁她的天空...
set fire to her skies in your private jets...
好了，她明白了    是啊，是啊，是啊
Okay, she gets it. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
用你们永无止境的欲望榨干她...
Bled her dry with your insatiable...
年轻人，我们在这里都想拯救世界，
Young man, we all want to save the world here,
但时间同样宝贵，你是在浪费我的时间
but time is also precious and you're wasting mine.
闭嘴，闪亮仔
Zip it, sparkles.
你为什么不停下嘬塑料吸管，
Why don't you stop sucking
来嘬这个呢！
on plastic straws, and suck on this!
尊敬的来宾们   我叫 J·丹尼尔·阿特拉斯
Honored guests. My name is J. Daniel Atlas.
你们可能记得我是你们个人最喜欢的
You may remember me as your personal favorite
四骑士魔术师
of the Four Horsemen of magic.
现在仔细看，
Now watch closely
看我将著名的 心之钻石 变到我的手掌上
as I make the famous Heart Diamond appear on my palm.
天哪，他一定像这位绿色和平组织的朋友一样
Geewhiz, he must be as starved
极度渴望关注
for attention as Greenpeace here.
阿布拉卡达布拉 阿莫-乌-娜-娜
Abracadabra, amor-oo-na-na
请放心，钻石绝对安全
Rest assured that the diamond is completely safe.
阿布拉卡达布拉 莫塔-乌-嘎-嘎
Abracadabra Morta-oo-ga-ga
是吗？
Is it?
阿布拉卡达布拉 阿布拉-乌-娜-娜
Abracadabra, abra-oo-na-na
现在，一个智者曾告诉我，其实就是对镜子里的自己说的，
Now, a wise man once told me, in the mirror, in fact,
呃，永远不要自以为是房间里最聪明的人，
uh, never assume you're the smartest person in the room,
她用她的语言说
In her tongue she said
“今夜 非死即爱”
"Death or love tonight"
证明给我看
prove it.
请便
Be my guest.
阿布拉卡达布拉 阿布拉卡达布拉
Abracadabra, abracadabra
好的，那么，让我们看看能不能打开这个盒子
All right, well, let's see if we can get that case open.
呃... 阿布拉卡达布拉
Uh... Abracadabra.
阿布拉卡达布拉 阿布拉卡达布拉…
Abracadabra Abracadabra...
呵   不行   呃... 阿拉卡赞
Huh. Nope. Uh... Alakazam.
等等
Wait.
芝麻开门
Open sesame.
啊
Ah.
依然安然无恙在我这里
Still safe with me.
不   放松   嗯，放松，维罗妮卡
No. Relax. Mm, relax, Veronika.
现在，正如你们的广告喜欢提醒我们的那样，
Now, as your ads like to remind us,
钻石恒久远
diamonds are forever.
护送她到安全地方   立刻！ 你拦住他！拦住他！
Get her to safety. Now! You stop him! Stop him!
拦住他！
Stop him!
杰克    嘿
Jack. Hey.
你在这里干什么？ 救你的命
What are you doing here? Saving your ass.
啊    不客气
Ah. You're welcome.
你也有一个   呵
You got one, too. Huh.
嗨   我是琼    是啊
Hi. I'm June. Yeah.
她是谁？抱歉，她是和我们一起的
Who's she? Sorry, she's with us.
钻石在哪里？
Where is the diamond?
什么？
What?
我猜你们这些家伙根本不在乎环境
I guess you guys don't care about the environment.
你比看起来要强壮
You're stronger than you look.
嘿！
Hey!
快跑
Run away.
嘿！嘿，嘿！
Hey! Hey, hey!
站住！别让他们跑了！
Stop! Don't let them get away!
好了，现在怎么办？
Okay, what now?
我的卡片上只说要把你们救出来   我不知道
My card just said to get you out of there. I don't know.
亨莉·里夫斯？
Henley Reeves?
我有好多你的海报
I have so many posters of you.
你是我童年的... 好了，粉丝待会再说
You're my childhood... All right, fanboy later.
但确实，呃... 你知道，真的很高兴见到你
But it does, uh... You know, it is really nice to see you.
粉丝待会再说   我们得往上走
Fanboy later. We got to go up.
举起手来，不许动！
Put your hands up and don't move!
真是胡扯
This is some bullshit.
怎么回事？
What is happening?
贝多芬的D大调协奏曲
Beethoven's Concerto in D major.
胡扯，胡扯，胡扯！
Bullshit, bullshit, bullshit!
阿特拉斯，我倒想看看你
Atlas, I would like to see you
用比利时语催眠三个家伙
hypnotize three dudes in Belgian.
你是说法语吧
You mean Flemish.
好吧，这就说得通了
Okay, that explains it.
感人的重聚   我们得走了
Lovely reunion. We have to go.
亨莉·里夫斯！
Henley Reeves!
欢迎回来！ 谢谢
Welcome back! Thanks.
容我冒昧，你真是...
And may I say, you are...
好了，走吧！ 是啊，是啊，是啊，是啊，是啊！
Okay, come on, let's go! Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
我是在赞美她，
I was paying her a compliment
因为见到她很高兴，只是见到她
because it was nice to see her, and only her.
我是... 我们明白！
I was... We get it!
在上面
Up there.
哇！哇！哇！那是来接我们的吗？
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa! Is that for us?
你看到还有其他人在试图逃跑吗？
Do you see any other people trying to escape?
快点，快点   走，走！
Come on, come on. Go, go!
快点，快点
Come on, come on.
呃，它一直在我手里
Uh, it was in my hand
从未...
the whole time. It never...
他们没有调换钻石
They didn't swap the diamond.
他们调换了盒子
They swapped the case.
而你，女士，离得够远了
And you, ma'am, are far enough.
你为什么不停下嘬塑料吸管，
Why don't you stop sucking on plastic straws,
来嘬这个呢！
and suck on this!
尊敬的来宾们...
Honored guests...
芝麻开门
Open sesame.
依然安然无恙在我这里
Still safe with me.
钻石恒久远
Diamonds are forever.
莱塔博    什么事，女士？
Lethabo. Yes, ma'am?
我们会让他们后悔的
We're going to make them regret this.
而且是加倍的
And then some.
马克·施赖伯，《名利场》
Marc Schreiber, Vanity Fair.
我错过了什么？
What did I miss?
你知道，我以为它会更闪亮
You know, I thought it'd be shinier.
好了   好吧，还回来
Okay. All right, give it back.
你在干什么？ 哦   抱歉   太滑了
What are you doing? Oh. Sorry. It's so slippery.
嘿   嘿    接着
Hey. Hey. Heads up.
好了，别再那么做了
Okay, don't do that again.
嘿，我能提一下，呃，房间里那个幼稚的家伙吗？
Hey, can I address the, uh, infant in the room?
呃... 这些人是谁？
Uh... Who are these guys?
这些就是那帮美妙的孩子，他们用深度伪造技术冒充了我们的演出
These are the wonderful kids that deepfaked our show.
什么？ 阿特拉斯：是的
What? ATLAS: Yeah.
是你派警察到我家的？
You had the cops sent to my house?
你吓到我孩子了    是啊，抱歉
You freaked out my kids. Yeah, sorry.
抱歉    抱歉
Sorry about that. Sorry about that.
孩子们怎么样？
How are the kids, though?
你离开我们去过的那种无聊的郊区生活怎么样？
How is the whole boring suburban life you left us for?
嘿，冷静点，伙计   你错过了机会
Hey, relax, man. You missed your shot.
嗯    看到那颗石头的大小了吗？
Hmm. See the size of that rock?
不，让我看看
No, let me see that.
哦，虽然不是心之钻石，但也令人印象深刻
Ooh, it's no Heart Diamond, but it's impressive.
我已经告诉过你了，丹尼   我当时怀孕六个月，
I already told you, Danny. I didn't feel safe
我不觉得倒挂着从紧身衣里逃脱是安全的
trying to escape from a straitjacket hanging upside down.
我那时怀孕六个月    得了吧
I was six months pregnant. Come on.
我们最后会把你翻回来的    你不会有事的
We would have flipped you right side up at the end. You'd have been fine.
得了吧    你们根本没想过我
Come on. You guys didn't even miss me.
你们花多久就找人替代我了？一个下午？
How long did it take you to replace me? An afternoon?
嗯，大概花了大半个晚上
Um, and the better part of an evening.
嘿，说到这个，卢拉怎么样了？
Hey, speaking of, how is Lula?
你们俩还，呃... 不
Are you guys still, uh... No.
她，呃... 她搬到巴黎去了
She, uh... she moved to Paris.
哦，不   她甩了伟大的 J·怀尔德   我的天
Oh, no. She dumped the great J. Wilder. My God.
我很抱歉   我道歉
I'm sorry. My apologies.
你不是应该在某艘游轮上羞辱自己吗？
Don't you need to be on some, like, cruise ship somewhere humiliating yourself?
羞辱自己？ 是的
Humiliating myself? Yeah.
我每趟游轮收入五位数，外加额外福利
I make five figures per cruise, plus perks.
"外加额外福利   " 他说，"外加额外福利   "
"Plus perks." He said, "plus perks."
我以为梅里特在墨西哥酗酒度日
And I thought Merritt drinking himself
已经够让人沮丧的了   哦
to death in Mexico was depressing. Ooh.
说到这个，我得回去继续了
Speaking of, I got to get back to it.
这肝脏不会自己毁掉自己的
This liver's not gonna destroy itself.
呃，我们能停一下吗？
Uh, can we dry dock this thing?
等等，等等   你要走了？
Wait, wait, wait. You're leaving?
嗯，是啊，我是说，叙旧很开心
Well, yeah, I mean, great catching up.
嗯，我不知道，什么，十年后再见？
Um, I don't know, what, see you in another ten?
很高兴认识你们，小蝌蚪们
Nice to meet you, little tadpoles.
再见
Adios.
是啊，你知道吗？我也要走了
Yeah, you know what? I'm out of here, too.
我有个演出要赶
I have a gig to get to.
真的吗？他们会报销你的优步车费吗？
Really? They're covering your Uber?
签了保密协议   一个字都不能说
Signed an NDA. Can't say a word.
你在干什么？
What are you doing?
六个把手，没一个能打开它
Six handles and none of them open it.
你以为你在跟谁说话？让开
Who do you think you're talking to? Move.
我很抱歉，但我真的不太清楚
I'm sorry, but I don't really know
你们之间是怎么回事
what's going on with you guys.
我感觉这里有很多奇怪的历史，
I'm getting the feeling there's a lot of weird history here,
气氛有点尴尬
and things are a little awkward.
是啊，伙计们，你们曾经是骑士
Yeah, you guys, you used to be the Horsemen.
我不明白   你们为什么分手了？
I don't get it. Why did you break up?
问他们   问他们为什么我们分手了
Ask them. Ask them why we broke up.
如果由我决定，我们不会分手的
If it was up to me, we wouldn't have.
天眼想让我们... 不，不
The Eye wanted us to... No, no.
揭露一个俄罗斯军火商
expose a Russian arms dealer.
我们真的需要再经历一遍这个吗？
Do we really have to live through this again?
我们犯了一些大错，我们变得...
We made some huge mistakes, we got...
草率了    自大了
Sloppy. Cocky.
因为我们，迪伦·施赖克再也
Because of us, Dylan Shrike will never see
无法走出俄罗斯的监狱了
the outside of a Russian prison again.
谁？ 迪伦·施赖克   好吗？
Who? Dylan Shrike. Okay?
他是骑士之一   拜托   做做功课，伙计
He's a Horseman. Come on. Do your homework, man.
我很抱歉   伙计们，我不知道
I'm so sorry. Guys, I had no idea.
什么，他被永远困在里面了？
What, he's stuck in there forever?
这显然是个悲剧，
Which is obviously a tragedy
是我永远无法原谅自己的事情
and something I'll never forgive myself for.
我很抱歉   伙计们，我完全不知道
I'm so sorry. Guys, I had no idea.
什么，他要永远关在里面了？
What, he's stuck in there forever?
显然这是个悲剧
Which is obviously a tragedy
他永远被困在那里了？
也是我永远无法原谅自己的事
and something I'll never forgive myself for.
这显然是个悲剧，也是我永远无法原谅自己的事
我也不会原谅你   对，好吧
Nor will I. Yeah, fine, man.
我也不会原谅   是啊，好吧
但这并不意味着你们必须解散
But it didn't mean you have to quit.
但并不意味着你们必须解散
伙计，这真是，呃……
Man, that is, uh...
这真的挺糟心的，伙计们   很抱歉
It's really a bummer, guys. Sorry about that.
“挺糟心的”？
"A bummer"?
我……我……我喜欢你们这代人
I... I... I love the way
总结事情时那种“雄辩”的方式
your generation sums things up so eloquently.
我是说，谁来给我解释一下
I mean, someone explain to me
为什么这几个未成年小孩会在这里
why these prepubes are even here.
和你一样的原因，伙计
Same reason you are, man.
天眼想要他们
The Eye wanted 'em.
好吧，我们拿到“心之钻”了
Well, we got the Heart.
天眼接下来想让我们做什么？不知道
What does The Eye want us to do next? No idea.
我只知道一件事
I know one thing.
你手里拿着一颗价值五亿的钻石   是啊，可能吧
You've got a half a billion dollar diamond in your hands. Yeah, probably.
他们会联系我们的   是的，很可能
They're gonna get in touch. Yeah, probably.
等等，阿特拉斯，我能看看你的卡吗？
Whoa, wait, wait. Atlas, can I see your card?
嗯
Yeah.
哇   是张地图
Hmm. It's a map.
嘿，阿特拉斯，是你爸爸   不，这是……
Hey, Atlas, it's your dad. No, it's...
这是一张只有当四骑士齐聚时才会显现的地图
It's a map that only reveals itself when the Horsemen are together.
做梦吧   真的吗，老兄？
Fat chance. Really, dude?
我是说，得了吧，
I mean, come on,
天眼显然是想让你们来做这件事
The Eye obviously wants you guys to do this.
你们是四骑士   拿出点样子来
You're the Horsemen. Start acting like it.
好吧
All right.
我想罗萨里托可以等几天
I suppose Rosarito can wait a couple days.
我……我可以试着重新安排这个演出
I... I can try to reschedule this gig.
虽然不容易，但我会想办法的
It's not gonna be easy, but I'll figure it out.
我是说，我有点怀念和你们一起
I mean, I have kind of missed running for my life
逃命和跳屋顶的日子了
and jumping off roofs with you guys.
欢迎回来   谢谢
It's good to have you back. Thanks.
那么，这个地方是哪里？
Okay, so where is this place?
我们来这里到底要做什么？
What are we supposed to be doing here?
天眼会让我们知道的
The Eye will let us know.
好了，拍照时间   你在干嘛？
All right, picture time. What are you doing?
拍张照   现在情侣都这么干
Taking a photo. That's what couples do now.
请不要把顶级秘密地点的
Please don't post photos
照片发出去   别嫉妒
of the top secret location. Don't be jealous.
我知道你也想入镜
I know you want to be in it.
是啊，我不想入镜
Yeah. I don't want to be in it.
因为这可能被用作……用来留念
Because it can be used for... For memories.
不，不是留念   是证据
No, not memories. Evidence.
哈   我从没见过这样的门
Huh. I've never seen a door like this.
好吧，我打不开
Okay, I can't open it.
看你的了，杰克？
You got this, Jack?
等等   你是指“琼”吗？
Wait. Don't you mean "June"?
杰克才是我们的开锁专家   哇哦
Jack's our lockpick. Whoa.
看来有场良性竞争
Looks like a little healthy competish.
得了吧，这不公平
Come on, this isn't fair.
我开锁的时候她还没出生呢
I've been picking locks since before she was born.
让我找找锁眼
Let me find the keyhole.
可能在另一面   对，在下面
Maybe the other side. Yeah, it's underneath.
你现在可没给我什么信心，杰克
You're not inspiring confidence right now, Jack.
他能行的   嗯
He's got it. Hmm.
他能行的   手生了？
He's got it. Feeling rusty?
别催我
Don't rush me.
他什么时候开始开锁？
When does he start the lock picking?
嘿，杰克，我觉得这锁不是用撬的
Hey, Jack, I don't think this is a lock you pick.
我觉得这锁得用解的   所以……
I think it's a lock you solve. So...
给他示范一下该怎么做
Show him how it's done.
哇哦
Whoa.
你介意我快点解开它吗？
Do you mind if I just figure this out real quickly?
好吧
Okay.
如果你玩过密室逃脱，
If you've ever done an escape room,
你就会知道有各种各样的谜题
you'd know there are all kinds of different puzzles.
不光是锁和钥匙的事
It's not just about locks and keys.
哇哦   阿特拉斯：哈
Whoa. ATLAS: Huh.
你也许该更新下你的技术了，杰克
You might want to update your game, Jack.
哇哦
Whoa.
不过，请带路吧
But, by all means, lead the way.
我觉得是他先把锁弄松了，真的
I think he loosened it for her, ultimately.
哈   哦
Huh. Ooh.
哇哦   哇
Whoa. Wow.
呃，这是什么地方？
Uh, what is this place?
魔术宅男的天堂
Magic nerd heaven.
P·T·塞尔比特的棺材？
P.T. Selbit's coffin?
看吧？
See?
伙计们，胡迪尼的拘束衣
Guys, Houdini's straitjacket.
是的，确实是
Yes, it is.
嘿，为了怀旧，我能把你放进去吗？
Hey, can I put you in here for old time's sake?
不行   不行？
No. No?
我觉得挺有意思的
I thought it was funny.
多谢   你想进来吗？
Thanks a lot. You wanna come in?
不   好吧
No. Right.
查理，看看这个，伙计
Charlie, check this out, dude.
这是什么？
What is it?
接子弹
Bullet catch.
不可能！
No way!
哟！
Yo!
死胡同？是的，死胡同
Dead end? Yeah, dead end.
嘿，伙计们，死胡同
Hey, guys, dead end.
或者，是吗？嗯
Or, is it? Hmm.
哦，我的天
Oh, my God.
是的，没错
Yeah, it is.
嗯，这很奇怪
Hmm, that's weird.
骰子应该在这里，球应该在这里
The die should be here and the ball should be here.
哇   干得漂亮
Whoa. Well played.
没什么
It's nothing.
四行
Four rows.
一、五、八、四？是密码吗？
One, five, eight, four? Is it a code?
一、一、五、六、十八……减四
One, one, five, six, 18... Minus four.
一、八、九？一千五百八十四
One, eight, nine? Fifteen, eightyfour.
1584   什么……
1584. Wha...
《巫术的发现》
The Discoverie of Witchcraft.
这是第一本关于舞台魔术的书
It's the first book on stage magic.
这是它的出版年份
It's when it was published.
天哪，他怎么知道这个？
God, how does he know that?
呃，他基本上就是个装满无用信息的电脑
Uh, he's basically a computer full of useless information.
哈
Huh.
“无用”？
"Useless"?
这很酷
This is cool.
不可思议   不错
Unreal. Nice.
嘿，伙计们，这是城堡的平面图
Hey, guys, it's the floor plan of the chateau.
但好像有点不同
But it's different somehow.
上是下
Up is down.
左是右
Left is right.
连房间都是魔术
Even the rooms are tricks.
我的骑士们
My Horsemen.
塔迪厄斯！
Thaddeus!
见到你真好   见到你真好，亲爱的
So good to see you. So good to see you, darling.
你本可以看看门铃摄像头给我们开门的
You could've just checked the Ring camera and buzzed us in.
那样有什么乐趣呢？
Now, where's the fun in that?
先生   嗨，我是查理
Sir. Hi, I'm Charlie.
我是你的超级粉丝   嗨，查理
I'm such a big fan of yours. Hi, Charlie.
呃……
Um...
我从没见过这么大的卢博透镜实物
I've never seen a Lubor Lens this big in person.
真的？那你还没见过更厉害的呢
Really? Well, you ain't seen nothing yet.
那么塔罗牌是你寄的？
So you sent the tarot cards?
不是
No.
不，我早就放弃这种蠢事了，
No, I've long since given up such foolishness,
以及你们集体的不和谐
and your collective dysfunction.
不，我现在唯一表演的魔术
No, the only magic I do nowadays
是给我的孙子孙女们看的
is for my grandchildren.
不过几周前，
Some weeks ago, however,
确实有一张卡片出现在我家门口，
a card did appear on my doorstep,
提醒我为七名即将成为法律逃犯的人
warning me to prepare this chateau
准备好这座城堡
for the arrival of seven soontobe fugitives
这说得通
from the law.
说得通   是的
That tracks. Yeah.
等等，那天眼为什么想让我们来这里？
Wait, so why does The Eye want us here?
我只能推测，无论他们接下来
Well, I can only assume that whatever it is
想让你做什么，
they want you to do next
都藏在这墙里的某个地方
is hidden somewhere in these walls.
看，这座城堡，鲁西永城堡，
See, this chateau, Chateau Roussillon,
曾经是他们的家
used to be their home.
1943年，
In 1943,
盟军需要从各个来源获得军事奇迹
the Allies needed military miracles from every source.
他们求助于
They enlisted the aid
当时一些最有才华的魔术师
of some of the most talented magicians of the time.
他们用泥土、纸板、灯光和数千个充气橡胶坦克
They built a whole city using mud, cardboard, lights,
建造了一座完整的城市，
thousands of inflatable rubber tanks
来误导德国人
to misdirect the Germans.
贾斯珀·马斯克林的天才之作
The genius of Jasper Maskelyne.
有人了解这段历史
Somebody knows his history.
等等，那纳粹跟钻石有什么关系？
Wait, so, what do the Nazis have to do with the diamond?
这个，我就不知道了
That, I do not know.
但答案就在这里的某个地方
But the answer is here somewhere.
我们只需要开始找
We just have to start looking.
范德伯格女士   范德伯格女士
Ms. Vanderberg. Ms. Vanderberg.
您如何回应关于贵公司只是洗钱前台的
How do you respond to the rumors that your company
传闻？
is nothing but a front for money laundering?
四骑士是窃贼，
The Horsemen are thieves
伪装成反资本主义的表演者，
posing as anticapitalist entertainers,
他们不公平地针对我和我的优秀公司
and they have unfairly targeted me and my good company.
我挑战任何诽谤我们的人，
I challenge anyone who maligns us to look
仔细审视我们的运营和账目
closely at our operations and our books.
我也挑战警方将这些魔术师
And I challenge police to put those magicians
送回他们该待的地方，过去
back where they belong, in the past.
好了，不再提问了
All right, no more questions.
不再提问了，谢谢！
No more questions, please! Thank you!
国际刑警说是内部人员作案
Interpol said it was an inside job.
窃贼清楚知道盲点在哪里
Thieves knew exactly where the blind spots were.
怎么样？让我猜猜
How was it? Let me guess.
你就是这些四骑士
You're the one behind these Horsemen
和他们那些小马仔的幕后主使
and their little stable hands.
不   我如果索要钻石，
No. Why would I ask for the diamond
然后又去偷它？
and then try to steal it?
如果我是你，我会想办法
If I were you, I'd figure out a way
把它拿回来，而且要快
to get it back, and fast.
我知道你和你的车队
I understand that you and your race team
本周晚些时候会在阿布扎比
will be in Abu Dhabi later this week.
一个完美的中立地带
A perfect neutral ground.
我会带上我的证据
I'll bring my evidence.
你带上你的“心之钻”，如果你有的话
You bring your Heart, if you have one.
找到他们了吗？我们确实有一些线索
Have you found them yet? We do have a few leads.
有人看到他们向南驶出比利时
They were seen headed south out of Belgium.
现在有消息说四骑士
Now they're saying the Horsemen
一小时前在法国出现过
have been seen in France one hour ago.
法国警察局长欠我人情
The head of the French police owes me.
打电话给他，就说我要这些四骑士的脑袋
Just call him and say that I want these Horsemen's heads
被装在盘子里端上来
served up on a platter.
宪兵会找到他们的   我确定
The gendarme will find them. I'm sure of it.
塔迪厄斯让我们找东西
Thaddeus told us to look for something.
你觉得是什么？
What do you think it is?
哦，哇   这很酷
Oh, wow. This is cool.
你话不多
You are not a big talker.
哦   抱歉
Oh. Sorry.
但你很爱道歉
But you are a big apologizer.
抱歉   我又来了
Sorry. I just did it again.
抱歉   我是说……我只是紧张
Sorry. I mean... I'm just nervous.
我是你们的超级粉丝
I'm a big fan of you guys.
我招来了警察，我真的……
And I got the cops called in, and I'm really...
我真的……我不说了
I'm really... I'm not gonna say it.
你被原谅了
You're forgiven.
而且你们让四骑士看起来很出色
And you guys made the Horsemen look good.
但我没看到你   你为什么不在里面？
But I didn't see you. Why weren't you in it?
哦，我只是……我更喜欢待在幕后，你知道的
Oh, I just... I prefer to be behind the scenes, you know.
我设计我们所有的魔术
I design all of our tricks.
呃，我们要去哪儿？我觉得我们迷路了
Um, where are we going? I feel like we're lost.
你是真的更喜欢那样，
Do you really prefer that,
还是那只是你用来掩饰的借口？
or is that just something you hide behind?
呃，你什么意思？
Uh, what do you mean?
嗯，我……哇哦
Well, I... Whoa.
多年来，我告诉自己我想当助手，
For years, I told myself I wanted to be an assistant,
我不介意被阿特拉斯抢风头，
that I didn't mind being upstaged by Atlas,
因为他太出色了
'cause he's so brilliant.
但实际上，我只是……我害怕
But really, I just... I was afraid.
我害怕成为焦点
I was afraid to take the spotlight.
哦   塔迪厄斯说得对   上是下
Ooh. Thaddeus was right. Up is down.
颠倒的房间   酷
Upside down room. Cool.
酷？
Cool?
没什么能让你觉得震撼吗？
Is nothing impressive to you?
所以我才说“酷”啊
That's why I said "cool."
你不知道酷是什么意思吗？
Do you not know what cool means?
好吧，我们试着弄明白
All right, let's just try to figure out
这个房间怎么运作，好吗？
how this room works, okay?
好
Yeah.
弄明白了
Figured it out.
当然   没错   你早就什么都知道了
Of course. That's right. You know everything already.
那么这次我又做错了什么？
So what did I do wrong this time?
啊，没有   抱歉
Ah, nothing. My apologies.
你很了不起   能看着你是我的荣幸
You're amazing. It's an honor to watch you.
有人告诉过你你是个控制狂吗？
Has anyone ever told you that you're a control freak?
是的   很多次
Yep. Many times.
哇！嘿！
Whoa! Hey!
我确实弄明白了
I did figure it out.
哇哦   哇
Whoa. Wow.
软糖起作用了
Gummies kicked in.
我想知道我们在找什么
I wonder what we're looking for.
任何奇怪的东西
Anything weird.
这里的一切都很奇怪   天啊
This is all weird. Jesus.
看这个
Look at this.
你知道，我一直很敬佩你
You know, I have always looked up to you.
哦，是吗？
Oh, yeah?
是的，在你成为游轮魔术师之前
Yeah, before you became a cruise ship magician.
嘿，我也做企业活动
Hey, I also do corporate events.
哦，不会吧   我看不出来
Oh, no way. I couldn't tell.
那完全是浪费时间   现在怎么办？
So that was a total waste. What now?
一个魔术   好吗？不要魅力，
One trick. Okay? No charm,
不要口才   就一个魔术
no gifts of gabs. Just one trick.
伙计，我不需要向你证明自己
Dude, I do not have to prove myself to you.
我是说，你确实需要
I mean, you kind of do.
给我看看天眼为什么选你
Show me why The Eye picked you.
你知道吗？
You know what?
向我证明你不需要保姆
Prove to me that you don't need a babysitter.
哦，什么，现在你不表演了？
Oh, what, now you stop performing?
因为你的怪胎朋友们不在这儿，你就不炫耀了？
You're done showing off 'cause your misfit friends aren't here?
他们是我的家人   嗯哼
They're my family. Mmhmm.
你少来   我不需要让他们印象深刻
Don't you dare. I don't have to impress them.
好吧，算了   忘了吧
All right, fine. Forget it.
我只是想看看，当你不试图赢得廉价掌声时，
I just wanted to see what you were capable of
你到底有多大本事，
when you weren't trying to win cheap applause,
但我想答案是“一无是处”
but I guess the answer is nothing.
好吧   你想看魔术吗？
All right. You wanna see a magic trick?
看，你的问题在于，阿特拉斯，
See, the problem with you, Atlas,
你就是喜欢把事情搞复杂，伙计
is that you just like to overcomplicate things, man.
找一颗钻石比你想象的要容易得多
It is a lot easier to find a diamond than you think.
哦   然后让它……
Ooh. And to make it...
消失
disappear.
不错   检查一下你的口袋
Nice. Check your pocket.
真的吗？是的
Really? Yeah.
嗯
Hmm.
哦，不错   卡牌出现在不可能的位置
Ooh, not bad. Card to impossible location.
但别在棋盘上下跳棋，
But don't play checkers on a chessboard
因为我早已领先你五步
because I'm already five steps ahead of you.
检查你的口袋
Check your pocket.
嘿
Hey.
那些是无价古董   是的
Those are priceless antiques. Yeah.
这个房间是旧遗物
This room is where old relics
最终安息的地方
go to their final resting place.
是的   你，呃……你可能是对的，塔迪厄斯
Yep. You are, uh... You're probably right, Thaddeus.
但是，呃，在它们最终安息前，还有最后一次绽放光芒的机会
But, uh, not before they have one last shot at glory.
这里发生什么了？挺不错的，
What's going on here? Pretty good,
但你应该试着放慢一点
but you should try to do things a little more slow.
真的吗？
Really?
让你的观众享受真正的魔术
Let your audience enjoy the real magic.
好吧，
Okay,
不错，不错   哇
not bad. Not bad. Wow.
干得好，博斯科
Nice one, Bosco.
我扑克一直打得不好，
I've never been great at poker,
但方块会被红心压制吗？
but is a diamond trumped by a heart?
哦   在那儿呢   呼
Ooh. There it is. Whoo.
不错的误导，但是，别忘了
Nice misdirection, but, let's not forget
这究竟是为了什么   我还没完
what this is really about. I wasn't done.
给他们看看，查理   让一颗宝石消失
Show 'em, Charlie. Making a jewel disappear.
让我们看看这个   好吧
Let's see this one. All right.
盯紧目标
Keep your eye on the prize.
转啊转啊转，它们停在哪里，没人知道
Round and round they go, where they stop, nobody knows.
消失无踪了   哦
Good as gone. Ooh.
黑艺术，桌子做过手脚，我进来时就看到了
Black art, table's rigged, saw it when I came in.
是时候干净利落地脱身了   哦，是的
Time for a clean escape. Oh, yeah.
他去哪儿了？我知道他要干什么
Where is he going? I know what he's doing.
玩偶盒？那是魔术？
Jack in the box? That's a trick?
啊，是老把戏了
Ah, it's old stuff.
早知道甩掉他这么容易
If I had known he was that easy to get rid of.
没那么容易   是的，杰克
Not that easy. Yeah, Jack.
哦！好吧，热身表演够多了，
Ohh! Okay, enough of the warmup act,
该主角上场了
time for the headliner.
我想让你们从这些牌里想一张，
I want you to think of one of these cards,
但别想你以为我想让你想的那张
but don't think of the one you think I want you to think of.
想好了吗？是的，想好了
Got one? Yeah, I got one.
你的牌是什么？红心四
What was your card? Four of hearts.
哈哈
Haha.
不错，教授   我印象深刻   我印象深刻
Nice one, professor. I'm impressed. I'm impressed.
嘿   嘿   嘿   这威士忌比你还老
Hey. Hey. Hey. That whiskey is older than you.
对不起，老大   非常抱歉
Sorry, boss. So sorry.
听着，伙计们，我不说谎
Look, you guys, I'm not gonna lie.
这真的很酷
This has been really cool.
真的，真的很酷   去给他们露一手
Really, really cool. Go show 'em.
但是，呃，我想让它再酷一点
But, uh, I think I just want to make it a little cooler.
来吧，耶！嘿
Come on now, yeah! Hey.
她来了   没错！中国暴风雪
There she goes. Yes! Snow storm in China.
好了   漂亮
There we are. Beautiful.
冬天我总是穿白色，伙计们
I always wear white in winter, guys.
法国这个地区很少下雪，
Snow is rare in this part of France,
但是，结冰，那根本不可能
but, ice, that is just impossible.
经典   琼：不错
Classic. JUNE: Nice.
你怎么能把消失术做得这么好？
How do you do a vanish so good?
哦，魔术师从不揭秘   嗯？
Oh, a magician never tells. Hmm?
哦   嗯   检查
Ooh. Hmm. Check.
老兄？
Mate?
该死
Shit.
面对现实吧，博斯科
Face it, Bosco.
智慧和技巧总能战胜年轻和傲慢
Wisdom and skill overcome youth and arrogance every time.
谢谢
Thank you.
永远不要假设你是房间里最聪明的人   证明它
Never assume you're the smartest guy in the room. Prove it.
得了吧，伙计   你什么也没证明
Give me a break, man. You didn't prove anything.
嘿，我能提醒一下大家吗
Hey, can I just remind everyone
我们还没弄明白
we still haven't figured out
我们到底为什么在这个二战遗迹里？
why we're even in this World War II relic?
等等！
Wait!
贾斯珀·马斯克林，
Jasper Maskelyne,
那个……那个击败纳粹的魔术师
the... the magician who vanquished the Nazis.
他建造了假城市，假坦克
He built fake cities, fake tanks.
我是说……我在想……
I mean... I wonder...
哇   哦
Whoa. Oh.
哦，哇
Oh, wow.
哦，天哪，我说对了？
Oh, my God, I was right?
嘿，魔术入门，伙计，魔术成功时
Hey, Magic 101, man, never act surprised
永远不要表现得惊讶
when the trick actually works.
哦，抱歉
Oh, sorry.
哦，我的天   那些都是什么？
Oh, my goodness. What is all that?
纳粹战犯百科全书
Encyclopedia of Nazi war criminals.
呃，里面显然包括薇罗妮卡的爸爸
Uh, which apparently includes Veronika's dad.
二战后，幸存的纳粹逃往世界各地
After World War II, surviving Nazis fled around the world.
我不是会计师，但看起来彼得·范德伯格
I'm not an accountant, but looks like Peter Vanderberg
通过清洗他们的脏钱发了财
got rich cleaning their dirty money.
是的，而且显然薇罗妮卡接手后
Yeah, and apparently Veronika took over
利用他的犯罪网络继续他的勾当
right where he left off using his criminal network.
但是……但是我不明白
But... But I don't understand.
天眼想让我们用这个做什么？
What does The Eye want us to do with this?
嗯，如果我没猜错的话，
Well, if I'm not mistaken,
天眼想让我们揭露范德伯格家族的真面目，
The Eye wants us to unmask the Vanderbergs,
用一次巧妙的手法，
bring down two generations of criminals
扳倒两代罪犯
with a single sleight of hand.
我在网上读到一些关于范德伯格家族的有趣传闻
I've read some interesting rumors
关于范德伯格家族的
about the Vanderbergs online.
看起来15年前，维罗妮卡的母亲自杀了，
Looks like 15 years ago, Veronika's mom killed herself,
一周后，他们家的管家刹车失灵了
and a week later, their housekeeper's brakes failed.
她的车撞毁了，她和儿子都死了
Her car crashed, she and her son died.
当时有一些谋杀的嫌疑，
There was some suspicion of foul play,
但从未得到证实
but nothing was ever proven.
嗯
Hmm.
哦，该死
Oh, shit.
警察！
Police!
等等，等等，等等
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
听好了   分头走
Listen closely. Split up.
找个出口   快走   快   好的   来，我们走
Find a way out. Go. Go. Okay. Come on, let's go.
他说得对   大家分头走
He's right. Everybody split up.
好的，我们走
Okay, let's go.
这边，走这边！
This way, this way!
站住！
Stop!
转过身来   转过身来
Turn around. Turn around.
你听到他说的了，博斯科   转过身来
You heard him, Bosco. Turn around.
他们来了！
Here they come!
再见，我的朋友
Adios, mon ami.
抱歉！
Sorry!
你好，先生   你好
Bonjour, monsieur. Bonjour.
你知道，通常我喜欢给新客人
You know, normally, I like to give
一个正式的参观
a proper tour to new guests.
我猜你们已经发现
I suspect you've discovered
这栋房子藏着许多秘密
that this house holds many secrets.
塔迪厄斯！
Thaddeus!
想看我表演个魔术吗？
Would you like to see a magic trick?
要不我把自己变……
How about if I make myself...
消失？
disappear?
别动！
Don't move!
塔迪厄斯！
Thaddeus!
快！这边！
Hurry! This way!
塔迪厄斯？
Thaddeus?
哦，谢天谢地
Oh, thank God.
嘿，从这里出去最快的路是哪条？
Hey, which is the fastest way out of here?
绕过这个弯…… 嗯
Around this bend... Yeah.
有一条通道
there's a passageway.
沿着小溪穿过森林就行
Just follow the creek through the forest.
哇   哦！
Whoa. Oh!
哦，不   哦，不，不，不，不，不，不   不，不，不
Oh, no. Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no. No, no, no.
这不可能发生   起来，塔迪厄斯，站起来
This can't be happening. Come on, Thaddeus, stand up.
我们得走了
We're gonna go now.
你需要帮助
We need to get you help.
求你了，站起来
Please, stand up.
你们必须阻止维罗妮卡·范德伯格
You have to stop Veronika Vanderberg.
不，没有你我们做不到，塔迪厄斯
No, we can't do it without you, Thaddeus.
你们不需要我
You don't need me.
但你们需要彼此
But you do need each other.
永远别忘了这一点
Never forget that.
我来的时候就知道，这可能……
I knew when I came here, this was...
是我的最后一个魔术了
probably my final trick.
现在，别让我白白牺牲
Now, don't let me die in vain.
还有事情要做
There's work to be done.
走   现在就走，快走   求你们了
Go. Go now, go. Please.
趁还……
Before it's...
不晚
too late.
我们走吧   得走了
Let's go. We gotta go.
阿特拉斯！
Atlas!
警察把琼拘留了
The police took June into custody.
那杰克和梅里特呢？
Well, what about Jack and Merritt?
他们也一样   好吧，那我们把他们救出来
Them, too. Okay, so we break them out.
哇，呃呃   我们先稍微谈一谈
Whoa, uhuh. Let's just talk about this for a second.
谈什么？
Talk about what?
听我说   我们需要理智一点
Listen to me. We need to be smart.
不   我得把我的朋友从监狱里弄出来
No. We gotta get my friend out of jail.
博斯科…… 听着，你调查我们所有人那些事的时候，
Bosco... Look, when you were researching
你知道什么没被查出来吗？
all that stuff about us, you know what didn't come up?
查理和琼是我唯一的朋友
Charlie and June are my only friends.
你知道我真正喜欢他们什么吗？
You know what I really love about them?
他们不会让我觉得自己像个混蛋
They don't make me feel like an asshole.
我去救琼   博斯科，等等……
I'm getting June. Bosco, wait...
听我说   嘿   就等一下，兄弟
Listen to me. Hey. Just one second, dude.
听我说   你不能去
Listen to me. You can't.
为什么？告诉我
Why? Tell me.
他们在找你，博斯科
They're looking for you, Bosco.
他们在找我们所有人
They're looking for all of us.
是的   是的，你也会被捕的
Yes. Yes, you're gonna get arrested, too.
是的
Yes.
该死   没错
Shit. Exactly.
要是有别人
If only there was somebody else
疯狂到能实施一场越狱
crazy enough to stage a jailbreak
没有资源，没有保护
with no resources, no protection.
阿特拉斯   嗯？
Atlas. Yeah?
也许有
Maybe there is.
塔迪厄斯·马库斯·布拉德利，如果你有兴趣知道
Thaddeus Marcus Bradley, in case you're interested
你刚才谋杀的人的名字
in the name of the man you just murdered.
啊，是的
Ah, yes.
那真是不幸
That was unfortunate.
你知道，当这一切开始时，
You know, when this whole thing started,
我根本不在乎你或是你的钻石，
I didn't give a shit about you or your diamond,
但你却让这件事变得极其私人化
but you just went and made it deeply personal.
而现在，我非常期待将你扳倒
And now, I am really looking forward to taking you down.
我父亲会很喜欢你的
My father would have loved you.
他相当喜欢魔术
He was quite fond of magic.
在我五六岁的时候，
When I was five or six,
在我为数不多能独占他的时刻里，
in one of the few moments that I had him to myself,
他教了我一个戏法
he taught me a trick.
他会让一条红色丝绸手帕消失
He would make a red silk handkerchief disappear
然后又从他嘴里变出来
and then come back out of his mouth.
我爱死它了！
I loved it!
它有着恰到好处的花哨
It had just the right amount of flair.
我练习那个戏法练了好几个月
And I practiced that trick for months.
我以为只要我能做得足够好，
I thought that if I could do it just right,
我就能得到更多他的……
I would earn more of...
关注
of him.
但那只是假象
But that was the illusion.
从那以后我就讨厌魔术
I've hated magic ever since.
那种做作，那种俗套，更别提
The camp, the cheese, not to say anything
像你们这种用读心术的骗子了
of con artists like you with your mentalism.
我们俩都没有通灵能力，麦金尼先生
Neither one of us has psychic powers, Mr. McKinney.
但你不必拥有   你知道我的“心”在哪里
But you don't have to. You know where my Heart is.
我也不必拥有，
And I don't have to,
因为你会告诉我的
because you're going to tell me.
我想你足够聪明，应该知道
I think you're smart enough to know that
我他妈什么都不会告诉你，用我们德州人的话说
I ain't telling you shit, as we say in Texas.
而且，你对读心术的看法是错误的
And, you're wrong about mentalism.
人们把整个一生的故事都写在脸上
People wear their entire life story on their face.
你只需要知道如何解读
You just have to know how to read it.
拿你的脸来说吧
Take yours, for example.
可以吗？非常乐意
May I? With pleasure.
这会很有趣
This is gonna be fun.
嗯，你已经分享了，
Well, you've already shared,
那些折磨人的细节，关于你的“恋父情结”，
in excruciating detail, your daddy issues,
但我对你的母亲很好奇
but I'm curious about your mom.
她为什么要自杀？
Why did she commit suicide?
她也像你一样
Was she as desperate
渴望得到你父亲的关注吗？
for your father's attention as you were?
哦……
Ooh...
她是
She was.
那是为什么呢？
And why was that?
你父亲把注意力给了别人吗？
Did your father give his attention to someone else?
你把头发别到耳后时，那是个破绽
When you tuck your hair behind your ear, that's a tell.
他是
He was.
那么，他是在和他的秘书鬼混吗？
So, was he banging his secretary?
不，那太老套了
No, that's too cliche.
但一定是和你母亲亲近的人，才会让她……
But it had to be someone close to your mom for her to...
一个好朋友？美发师？
A good friend? Hairdresser?
不会是那个管家吧？
It wasn't the housekeeper, was it?
不，不是管家
No, not the housekeeper.
我没时间听这个
I don't have time for this.
人们通常在我要说到点子上的时候才这么说
And that's what people usually say when I'm getting hot.
我们是不是该把空调开大点，或者开个窗户？
Should we crank up the AC, maybe open a window?
现在，如果我父亲在和我的管家上床，
Now, if my dad was having sex with my housekeeper
而我母亲发现后自杀了，
and my mom found out and committed suicide,
我可能不会去剪断管家汽车的刹车线
I probably wouldn't cut the brakes on my housekeeper's car.
不过话说回来，我不是个精神病
But then again, I'm not a psychopath.
你是个可悲又可怜的男人
You are a sad and pathetic man.
我看得出你为什么想结束这一切
I can see why you want to end it.
呃，嘿，呃，维罗妮卡……
Uh, hey, uh, Veronika...
你知道，
You know,
走开也是一种破绽
walking away is also a tell.
哦啦啦
Oohlala.
先生，先生，先生
Monsieur, monsieur, monsieur.
她在哪？那女孩在哪？
Where is she? Where's the girl?
该死！
Shit!
她逃跑了
She escaped.
晚上好
Bonsoir.
这真是太恶心了，即使对你来说
That's pretty disgusting, even for you.
我想我可能葡萄酒喝多了
I think I may have overdone it on the wine.
嗨，卢拉
Hi, Lula.
顺便说一句，你看起来棒极了
You look great, by the way.
好吧，第一……
Okay, one...
我以为再也见不到你了
I didn't think I'd ever see you again.
你是怎么找到我们的？
How did you find us?
小鸟告诉我的
A little birdie told me.
想象一下我有多惊讶
Imagine my surprise.
你们居然都瞒着我重聚了
You guys all got back together without me.
什么？不，不是那样的   你不明白
What? No, it's not like that. You don't understand.
不是吗？不是？你自由了   混蛋
It wasn't? No?
You're free. Dick.
你自由了   混蛋
援兵到了
The cavalry.
想我吗？哦，想死了
Miss me? Oh, a lot.
哦，你好呀   是我，卢拉……
Oh, hello there. It's me, Lula...
提斯！卢拉！
Teeth! Lula!
记得吗？我也曾是四骑士之一
Remember? I too was once a Horseman.
是的，我问过你的事   我是唯一一个问的
Yeah, I asked about you. I was the only one.
哦，你是那个……他是唯一一个   真的吗？
Oh, you were the... He was the only one. Really?
该死   好吧
Shit. Okay.
我们得去会合点   好吧，计划是这样的
We have to get to the meetup. Okay, here's the plan.
我有接应车   都准备好了
I have the getaway car. It's all ready to go.
我只需要杰克去把它点着火
I just need Jack to hotwire it.
等等，你的计划是让我去偷车？
Wait, your plan is for me to steal a car?
嗯哼！
Uhhuh!
好吧，我去给车点火   你去救琼
Okay, I'll hotwire the car. You get June.
别丢下她，好吗？
Do not leave without her, all right?
外面见   好的，好的，好的   没问题
Meet us outside. Yeah, yeah, yeah. Okay.
哦！呃，注意警灯！
Oh! Uh, watch for flashing lights!
好的   你知道，我能给车点火……
Okay. You know, I can hotwire the...
你可以放开我了   对   抱歉
You can let go of me now. Right. Sorry.
哇！
Whoa!
法兰西万岁
Viva la France
我爱薯条和吐司
I love the fries and the toast
过来
Come here.
钻石在哪？
Where is the diamond?
梅里特，谢谢你
Merritt, thank you.
我罩着你，小子
Got your back, kiddo.
但谁罩着你呢？
But who's got yours?
警灯
Flashing lights.
快跑！
Run!
看着我的眼睛，
Look into my eyes,
看着并疑惑我为何低语
watch and wonder why I whisper words
会削弱你的意志 诱你入眠
that weaken your will, and sleep.
那些削弱你意志的话语，然后入睡
不是所有人都容易被催眠
Not everyone's susceptible.
我说，“睡！”
I said, "Sleep!"
请轻一点
Easy does it s'il vous plait.
嗒哒！
Tada!
喂？
Hello?
杰克？
Jack?
你可以告诉我们你是开警车来的
You could have told us you were coming in a police car.
非常感谢
Thank you very much.
而且，看，我们让第五骑士重现了
And, look, we made the Fifth Horseman reappear.
你好，卢拉   嗨
Hello, Lula. Hi.
好吧
Okay.
你没事吧？嗯   不，我没事   我没事
Are you okay? Yeah. No, I'm okay. I'm okay.
但他们抓住了梅里特   该死
But they have Merritt. Shit.
是的，我逃出来了，他没能逃掉   嗯，嗯
Yeah, I escaped, he couldn't. Yeah, yeah.
对这里的每个人来说都是情绪激动的时刻
Very emotional time for everybody here.
显然有很多事正在发生
Clearly a lot going on.
我真的尽量不把这一切当成是针对我个人的
And I'm really trying not to take any of this personally.
但是，拜托，能告诉我，
But, please, can you tell me,
天眼是直接联系你们的吗？
did The Eye contact you directly?
是的
Yeah.
你也一样？是的
You, too? Yes.
你为什么不早点联系我？我非常抱歉
Why didn't you call me sooner? I'm so sorry.
我得找个保姆   得了吧！
I had to find a babysitter. Come on!
一切都发生得太快了
Everything happened like that.
等等，抱歉   你们俩认识？
Wait, sorry. You two know each other?
是的   是的，我们认识……
Yeah. Yeah, we know...
你觉得世界上能有多少女魔术师？
How many female magicians do you think there are in the world?
现在这屋子里就有我们三个
The fact there are three of us in the room right now.
真是惊人   惊人
Shocking. Shocking.
这，简直，让人震惊   确实如此
It's, like, mind blown. That's true.
我很惊讶宇宙没有因此而坍缩
I'm surprised the universe isn't folding in on itself.
没错   阿布扎比！
Exactly. Abu Dhabi!
他总是这样吗？嗯嗯
Does he just do that? Mmhmm.
抱歉，我只是……顺便说一句，我是你的超级粉丝
Sorry, I just... I'm a big fan of yours, by the way.
我本来在琢磨维罗妮卡下一步会在哪里出现
I was trying to figure out where Veronika was gonna be next.
显然，范德伯格全球有一个赛车运动团队
And, apparently, Vanderberg Global has a motorsports team.
他们本周末将在阿布扎比推出一款新车
They're introducing a new car this weekend in Abu Dhabi.
这样我们就能救回梅里特并揭露她
So we can get Merritt back and expose her.
是的   是的
Yeah. Yeah.
不，不，不   我不是要揭露她
No, no, no. I am not exposing her.
我不会揭露任何人，好吗？
I am not exposing anyone, okay?
我不管天眼想要什么   不
I don't care what The Eye wants. No.
我们用这个交换梅里特，然后我们就完事
We are swapping this for Merritt, and then we are done.
我们是去救朋友，不是去拯救世界
We're saving our friend, we're not saving the world.
然后呢？什么？
And then what? What?
我们就回去过自己的生活，让她逍遥法外？
We just go back to our lives and let her walk away?
俄罗斯之后，你说过，“魔术师是娱乐者，
After Russia, you said, "Magicians are entertainers,
“不是超级英雄   ” 哦，天哪   又来了
"not superheroes." Oh, my God. Here we go.
我开始觉得你是对的
And I'm starting to think that you were right.
她不只是像她父亲那样洗钱
She doesn't just launder money like her father.
你看到了塔迪厄斯的下场
You saw what happened to Thaddeus.
显然，我现在有点跟不上节奏，对吧？
Obviously, I'm playing a bit of catchup here, right?
我没有掌握所有的信息，
I don't have all of the information,
但我认为这不应该阻止我
but I don't think that that should stop me
对我们下一步该做什么发表意见
from having an opinion about what we do next.
当然应该阻止   没错
Of course it should. Exactly.
不，不应该，阿特拉斯
No, it shouldn't, Atlas.
而且我认为我们应该揭露凡妮莎
And I think we should expose Vanessa.
维罗妮卡   维罗妮卡
Veronika. Veronika.
为了谋杀和……
For murder and...
另一件事是什么？洗钱
What is the other thing? Money laundering.
和洗钱
And for money laundering.
为了谋杀和洗钱
For murder and for money laundering.
是的   是的   我们应该把她绑起来……
Yeah. Yeah. We should tie her up...
不，不！太危险了！
No, no! It is too dangerous!
而且阿特拉斯是对的   什么？
And Atlas is right. What?
我们已经牺牲够多了
We are done sacrificing ourselves.
是的   抱歉   这不值得
Yeah. I'm sorry. It's not worth it.
胡说八道！
That's bullshit!
什么？你错了
What? You're wrong.
是吗？抱歉
Am I? Sorry.
不   别道歉   说出来
No. Don't be sorry. Say it.
你是   你错了   只是……
You are. You're wrong. It's just...
在我发现四骑士之前，
Before I discovered the Horsemen,
我对什么都漠不关心
I didn't give a shit about anything.
我……我的家人抛弃了我
I... My family gave me up.
我恨透了整个世界
I hated the whole world.
然后，我看到了你们的视频，
And then, I saw a video of you guys,
你们在努力让世界
and you were trying to make the world
少一些腐败，少一些糟糕
less corrupt, less terrible.
这让我开始在乎了
And that made me give a shit.
那么魔术是什么？
So what's the trick?
我保证这能行
I promise this is gonna work.
但障眼法足够了吗？
But is that enough misdirection?
只要她在这里而不是那里
As long as she's here and not there.
我们能搞定那个
We can take care of that.
哪怕你们只迟到五分钟……
If you're even just five minutes late...
五分钟？我觉得一分钟   一分钟迟到
Five? I'd say one. One minute late.
我们怎么知道会有足够多的人到场？
How do we know enough people are gonna show up?
伙计们，这已经火遍网络了
You guys, it's already viral.
我保证会有一大群人
I guarantee there'll be a crowd.
这太疯狂了   变数太多了
This is nuts. There's too many variables.
嘿，我们会和你保持联系
Hey, we'll be in constant contact with you
如果有什么意外…… 嘿，嘿，嘿
if something goes awry... Hey, hey, hey.
这里，几乎没有容错空间，伙计   好吗？零
There's, like, no margin for error here, man. Okay? Zero.
我们必须做到完美无瑕
We're going to have to be absolutely flawless
如果我们想成功实施如此冒险的计划
if we're gonna pull something this risky off
面对如此多的环节
with this many moving parts
在如此短得离谱的时间里，好吗？
in this ridiculously short amount of time, okay?
是的   嗯
Yes. Yeah.
但至少对我来说，
But speaking for myself, at least,
我觉得我们七个人的机会比大多数人都大
I think the seven of us have a better chance than most.
哦
Oh.
瞧瞧这是谁？
Would you look at this?
伟大的博斯科·勒罗伊什么时候心软了？
When did the great Bosco Leroy go soft?
好了，伙计们，我们干不干？
Okay, guys, are we doing this or what?
这是千万分之一的成功率
It is a ten million to one shot.
这种概率正合我意
Those are my kind of odds.
女士们先生们，
Ladies and gentlemen,
时刻已到
the time has come.
今晚，仅此一夜
Tonight, for one night only.
靠近点   再近点
Come in close. Closer.
因为你以为你看到的越多……
'Cause the more you think you see...
你就越容易被愚弄
The easier it will be to fool you.
倒计时开始
The countdown begins.
仅剩两小时，
In only two hours,
四骑士将首次同台演出，
the Four Horsemen will be on stage together
这是十年来的第一次
for the first time in ten years.
J·丹尼尔·阿特拉斯
J. Daniel Atlas.
亨莉·里夫斯
Henley Reeves.
杰克·怀尔德
Jack Wilder.
以及卢拉·梅
And Lula May.
女士们先生们，四骑士
Ladies and gentlemen, the Four Horsemen.
没错，骑士们回来了，仅此一夜
That's right, the Horsemen are back for one night only.
上周，我们偷走了心之钻石，
Now, last week, we stole the Heart Diamond,
而今晚，两小时后，
and tonight, in two hours' time,
我们将把它归还给其合法主人，
we're going to return it to its rightful owner,
也就是你们所有人
all of you.
你觉得这能引起她的注意吗？
Do you think that got her attention?
如果这都不能，我不知道还有什么可以了
If that didn't, I don't know what will.
好了，听着，既然你们已经知道
All right, listen, now that you know
事情到底能有多糟，
how bad things can actually get,
你们能不能就这一次试着稳妥行事？
can you please just try playing it safe this one time?
不能   好吧
No. Okay.
哦
Oh.
她来了   准时抵达
Here she is. Right on time.
欣赏得还愉快吗？
You enjoying the show?
呃，对我来说有点俗气
Eh, it's a little tacky for my taste.
我猜你们选择这个场地是因为它离我的场地近
I assume you chose your venue for its proximity to my own.
那么，好消息告诉你
Well, good news for you.
我把你列在我们的宾客名单上了
I've placed you on our guest list.
把我的“心”带来   我们做个交换
Bring me my Heart. We'll make an exchange.
麦金尼先生换钻石
Mr. McKinney for the diamond.
嗯嗯   外面，灯光下，
Mmhmm. Outside, under the lights,
别耍任何魔术花招
and not the first hint of magic.
只要有一只兔子从帽子里出来，
One rabbit comes out of a hat,
一张A牌从袖口滑出，
one ace slides out of a sleeve,
你的朋友就会“噗”的一声消失
and your friend goes poof.
只是用你能理解的行话来说
Just trying to use parlance you'd understand.
阿布拉卡达布拉 阿莫-乌-娜-娜
Abracadabra, amor-oo-na-na
阿布拉卡达布拉 莫塔-乌-嘎-嘎
Abracadabra Morta-oo-ga-ga
阿布拉卡达布拉 阿布拉-乌-娜-娜
Abracadabra, abra-oo-na-na
她用她的语言说
In her tongue she said
“今夜 非死即爱”
"Death or love tonight"
阿布拉卡达布拉 阿布拉卡达布拉
Abracadabra, abracadabra
阿布拉卡达布拉 阿布拉卡达布拉…
Abracadabra Abracadabra...
欢迎来到W亚斯岛
Welcome to the W Yas Island.
中东的奥兰多
The Orlando of the Middle East.
哈
Ha.
那么，最后，
Now, finally,
感谢亚斯岛举办这场活动
thank you to Yas Island for hosting an event
以匹配最快的赛车团队
worthy of the fastest team in motorsport.
这条赛道是顶尖的，
This track is elite,
但它很快将为我们竞争对手
but it will soon provide our competitors
提供赛道上最常见的景象，
with the most common view in racing,
那就是我们赛车的尾翼
the rear wings of our cars.
谢谢
Thank you.
我靠   那是维罗妮卡？
Holy shit. That's Veronika?
她很有领导气场
She has a very commanding presence.
我们魔术界的朋友们到了
Our magical friends have arrived.
你去迎接他们吧
Why don't you go and greet them?
非常感谢你们能来   希望你们享受比赛
Thank you so much for coming. I hope you enjoy the race.
好了，阿特拉斯说要制造混乱
Okay, Atlas said to create a distraction.
我们该怎么执行？
How are we gonna pull this off?
到处都是保安
There is security everywhere.
好了，伙计们，冷静   我来搞定
Okay, you guys, calm down. I got this.
你好   嗨
Hello. Hi.
呃，大卫   酷   我是媒体关系部的
Uh, David. Cool. I'm from media relations.
我只是来确认一下
I was just checking in.
你们能换个机位吗？
Do you think you guys could do a different camera placement?
好的，谢谢   继续
Okay, thanks. Continue.
那是谁？
Who is that?
该你了
Your turn.
动手吧
Let's do this.
务必确认
Make sure you confirm
钻石的真伪
the authenticity of the diamond.
这些人非常狡猾
These people are very tricky.
很高兴你来了
I'm so glad you came.
我们冰释前嫌如何？
What do you say we bury the hatchet?
插进彼此的脖子吗？哈！他真幽默
In each other's necks? Ha! He's funny.
我们各自拥有对方想要的东西
We each possess something beneficial to the other.
正是做交易的好理由
Perfect reason to do business.
只是，有一个条件
Only, there's one caveat.
我热切希望我们之间的来往到此为止
I fervently hope our mutual dealings are at a close.
她可真镇定   现在不是时候
She's so poised. Not now.
我恨她……呃   卢拉   嘘
I hate her... Ugh. Lula. Shh.
情况怎么样？兄弟，需要帮忙吗？
How's it going? Bro, can I help you?
是的，我们来拍车
Yeah, we're here to shoot the car.
哦，对   当然
Oh, right. Of course.
显然   给你证件
Obviously. There you are.
你的呢？呃，是的，
And you? Uh, yeah,
在我外套里某个地方
it's in my jacket somewhere.
找到了
There it is.
我们是《方格旗》纪录片剧组的
We're with Checkered Flags, the doc series.
下一季是关于范德伯格赛车的
Next season's on Vanderberg Motorsports.
他们真没跟你们打招呼？
They seriously didn't give you guys a headsup?
典型的
Typical.
我们只是拍点插入镜头，可能还有备用镜头
We're just gonna get some inserts, maybe some Broll
以及派对来宾惊叹这辆美车的镜头
and some party people gawking at this beauty.
好的，你们随时…… 喂，别碰车
All right, whenever you're... Oi, don't touch the car.
我们得拍内饰   是的
We got to shoot the interior. Yeah.
我其实可以让你在里面露个脸
I can actually get you a cameo in this thing.
省省吧   我有我的命令   是啊，我们也有我们的
Save it. I've got my orders. Yeah, and so do we.
晚上好，范德伯格女士
Good evening, Ms. Vanderberg.
是的   我们正试图拿到您要的素材，
Yeah. We're trying to get that footage you asked for,
但我们遇到了点小问题
but we ran into a little bit of a problem.
你会有麻烦的   她想跟你说话
You're gonna be in trouble. She wants to talk to you.
那可不好，伙计   嗯嗯   不好
That's not good, my guy. Mmmm. Not good.
你好
Hello.
听着，我父亲总说
Listen, my father always said
没人会不看货就买钻石
no one buys a diamond sight unseen.
此时此刻，我的车就是那颗钻石
And at this very moment, my car is the diamond.
所以，要么你让他们干活，
So, you can either let them do their job,
要么你就给自己找份新工作
or you can find yourself a new one.
抱歉耽搁了，女士
Sorry for the holdup, ma'am.
你们可以了   你太棒了
You're good. You're the best.
你能稍微往后退一点吗？
If you could just back up for me really quick?
为了打光   谢谢，伙计
Just for the light. Thanks, man.
那么，我们开始吧？
Well, shall we get on with it?
请
Please.
哦   当然，你带了个打手   请原谅
Oh. Of course, you have a goon. Forgive me.
啊，得了吧，你不相信我们？
Ah, come on, you don't trust us?
经历了这么多？
After all we've been through?
有问题吗？
Is there a problem?
不确定的话再检查一遍
Double check if you're not certain.
是“心之钻”   是的，当然是
It's the Heart. Yes, of course it is.
现在，拜托，能把我们的朋友带来了吗？
Now, please, can you get our friend?
来吧
Come on.
他在那儿   好的
There he is. Okay.
嘿
Hey.
呼   你还好吗？
Whew. You okay?
嗯，现在我知道我值五亿美元了
Well, now that I know I'm worth half a billion dollars.
我还是觉得我们被坑了，但见到你们真好
I still think we got ripped off, but it's good to see you.
一手交钱，一手交货
Signed, sealed, delivered.
瞧，我是个信守承诺的人
See, I'm a woman of my word.
想留下的话，就尽情享受派对吧
Stick around if you want, enjoy the party.
嘿！嘿！
Hey! Hey!
搞什么鬼？
What in God's name?
该死！让开！
Shit! Step aside!
快点，这玩意儿怎么开？
Come on, how do you make this thing go?
你朝我吼我没法集中精神！
I can't concentrate with you yelling at me!
别让他跑了！
Don't let him get away!
借过！
Excuse me!
报警！
Call the police!
表演看得还开心吗？
You enjoying the show?
你就站在那里干瞪眼还是去把我的车追回来？
You just gonna stand there gawking or get my car back?
是你干的
You did this.
好了，出发了
Okay, here we go.
好了，阿特拉斯，你想要分散注意力，
Okay, Atlas, you wanted a distraction,
这下注意力够分散了
you got a distraction.
伙计，这车尾巴真灵活
Man, this thing is tail happy.
哦，天哪，搞什么？
Oh, man, what the hell?
我们掉进了一个陷阱门之类的
We fell through a trapdoor or something.
大家都还好吗？
Is everybody okay?
我们在哪？不好
Where are we? No.
今早醒来时，只有一件事
When I woke up this morning, there was only one thing
比我的钻石更让我渴望
I wanted more than my diamond.
那就是我的骑士们被关起来
My Horsemen under lock and key.
现在两者我都拥有了，
And now that I have both,
我必须承认，我有点被宠坏了
I must admit, I'm feeling a little bit spoiled.
在你们准备你们的小表演时，
While you were prepping your little performance,
我也策划了一个我自己的戏法
I curated a trick of my own.
五位骑士被困，无处可逃
Five Horsemen trapped, no escape.
你们五位也许是国宝，
You five may be national treasures,
但我们这里也有国宝
but we have those here, too.
只是它们很难被找到，
Only they're hard to find,
因为它们被埋在沙子里
because they're buried in sand.
对世界来说，你们将看似死于
To the world, it will appear you died
一场失败的逃脱表演
in a failed escape act.
现在，让我们看点魔术吧
Now, let's see some magic.
去他妈的魔术！快叫人支援！
Fuck magic! Somebody call for backup!
杰克，打电话给琼   谁有信号？
Jack, call June. Anyone have service?
天哪，她一定屏蔽了手机信号
God, she must have scrambled the cell signal.
她把一切都想到了！
She thought of everything!
卢拉，你站哪边的？
Lula, whose side are you on?
我当然站在我们这边，但她确实把一切都想到了
I'm on our side, obviously, but she also thought of everything.
两件事可以同时成立
Both things can be true at one time.
沙子在升高   沙子在变多
The sand is getting higher. The sand is getting bigger.
沙子更多了，而且更大了
There's more sand and it's getting larger.
亨莉，亨莉，呃，逃脱第一原则
Henley, Henley, uh, first principle of escape.
呃，能存活多久？对
Uh, how long is it survivable? Right.
对   很好   根据沙流速度判断，
Right. Great. Judging from the rate of the flow,
这个箱子的体积……
the volume of the box...
呃，是的，我们完蛋了   哦，真棒
Uh, yeah, we're screwed. Oh, amazing.
好吧，那逃脱第二原则呢？
Okay, how about the second principle of escape then?
好的，那就是箱子本身
Okay, so that's the box itself.
有缺陷吗？有弱点吗？
Is there a flaw? Is there a weakness?
有后门吗？
Is there a back door?
大家快检查一下！
Everybody just needs to check!
这边是封死的
This side's sealed.
该死   不，封死了，封死了，封死了
Shit. No, it's sealed, sealed, sealed.
所有地方都封死了
Everything's sealed.
有没有第三原则的可能？
Any chance there's a third principle?
我有你想要的东西
I have what you're after.
完美
Perfect.
我们在“心”之所在处见面
I will meet you where the Heart resides.
我迫不及待了
I can hardly wait.
直接去金库
Straight to the vault.
不，不，不，不！成功了！
No, no, no, no! Yes!
救救我，瑞奇·鲍比！救救我！
Help me, Ricky Bobby! Help me!
现在就真的要这样了吗？
Is this really gonna happen right now?
我们就要死在这个盒子里了？真的吗？
We're just gonna die here in this box? Really?
真有意思   一周前，我还想死，
It's funny. A week ago, I wanted to die,
然后……然后我重新找到了活下去的理由，
and then... then I get my reason to live back,
现在，我们真的要死了
and now, we're actually gonna die.
这有什么好笑的？
How is that funny?
嗯，我是说，在我脑子里想的时候更好笑些
Well, I mean, it was funnier in my head.
这是……你知道，是一种奇特的好笑
It's... You know, it's peculiar funny.
不   呃呃   不
No. Uhuh. No.
我们没招了
We're out of options.
天哪，我真不该那么刻薄地评价你的网站，
God, I never should have been that horrible
你的服装和标志
about your website and your costumes and the logo.
好吧   “怀尔德”里的“I”是根小魔杖，
Okay. It's not embarrassing
这并不丢人
that the "I" in "Wilder" is a little magic wand.
我懂了   那是……是不丢人
I got it. That's... It's not.
谢谢   它很可爱，也很迷人
Thank you. It's cute and it's charming.
够了   而且我……我想你
That's enough. And I... I missed you.
听着，我知道我并不总是表现出来，但是，嗯……
Listen, I know I don't always show it, but, um...
我真的很看重你们所有人
I really do think the world of all of you.
真不敢相信我们要被活埋了
I cannot believe we're getting buried alive.
我是说，就像西部片一样   等等，等等   活埋
I mean, it's like a Western. Wait, wait. Buried alive.
那是，一种古老的魔术传统
That's, like, an old magic tradition.
抱歉，我们认识谁做过这个？
Sorry, who do we know who did that?
比尔·舍克差点死在那上面   记得吗？
Bill Shirk nearly died doing that. Remember?
他进了一个有机玻璃棺材，然后被沙子覆盖
He got into a Plexiglas coffin and had it covered in sand.
但有机玻璃不是破了吗？
But didn't the Plexiglas break?
沙子湿了   沙子湿了
The sand got wet. The sand got wet.
我想起来了   前一天晚上下雨了
I remember now. It rained the night before.
好吧，湿沙子比干沙子重   压碎了玻璃
Okay, wet sand is heavier than dry. It broke the glass.
等等，等等，等等   如果我们弄破那根管子，
Wait, wait, wait, wait. If we broke that pipe,
水就会弄湿沙子，
then it would wet the sand,
然后就能……就能压碎箱子，对吧？
and then it'll... it'll break the box, right?
如果我能……如果我能用什么东西缠住它，
If I could... If I could wrap something around it,
我或许能使得上劲
I might be able to get some leverage.
好的
Okay.
梅里特，把你的皮带给我
Merritt, give me your belt.
好的   好的，你拿到了   你拿到了
Okay. Okay, you got it. You got it.
是的，好的，好的   加油
Yep, okay, okay. Come on.
好，好，好   你能行
Good, good, good. You got this.
你能行   加油   加油
You got this. Come on. Come on.
成功了！成功了！成功了！
Yes! Yes! Yes!
救救我！救救我！把我拉下来！
Help me! Help me! Pull me down!
好的，好的   嗯，嗯，嗯   它是金属做的
Okay, okay. Yeah, yeah, yeah. It's made up of metal.
漂亮，漂亮，漂亮，好的
Nice, nice, nice, okay.
停车   你已经被包围了
Pull over. You have been surrounded.
我很想停车，
I'd love to pull over,
但我终于找到感觉了
but I'm finally getting the hang of this.
我是世界上最棒的司机！
I'm the greatest driver in the world!
不，不，不，不
No, no, no, no.
小心！
Watch out!
该死！
Damn it!
关掉引擎，下车
Turn off the engine and exit the vehicle.
你被包围了
We've got you surrounded.
举起手来，不许动！
Put your hands up and don't move!
抱歉   我是不是忘了打转向灯？
I'm sorry. Did I forget to use my blinker?
你被捕了
You're under arrest.
谢谢，先生们   干得漂亮
Thank you, gentlemen. Excellent work.
我们收到了对博斯科·勒罗伊的红色通缉令
We've had a red notice for one Bosco Leroy.
谢谢   不客气
Thank you. No problem.
唉，阿特拉斯会杀了我的
Yep, Atlas is gonna kill me.
水进得太快了   而且玻璃不破
Water's coming in too fast. And the glass won't break.
就为了一颗钻石   现在倒能用上它
All this for a diamond. We could use that now.
没什么比钻石更能切割玻璃了
Nothing cuts glass like a diamond.
等等，哇，哇   等等，亨莉   亨莉
Wait, whoa, whoa. Wait, Henley. Henley.
对了！我能憋气八分钟
Yes! I can hold my breath for eight minutes.
如果有人能带我们出去，那就是我们了
If anyone can get us out of this, we can.
我们正驶入沙漠，女士
We're crossing into the desert, ma'am.
沙尘暴越来越大了
The dust storm is getting worse.
他怎么会在这儿？
What's he doing here?
范德伯格女士被你和你的朋友们偷走的钻石？
Ms. Vanderberg's diamond that you and your friends stole?
丢了什么东西吗？
Lost something?
真有趣
That was fun.
成功了！成功了
It's working! It's working.
大家都来帮忙！
Everybody help!
大家都来帮忙！一起用力！加油！
Everybody help! Let's do it! Come on!
加油
Come on.
亨莉，干得漂亮！
Henley, way to go!
哦，天哪！干得好！
Oh, my God! Nice job!
好了，我们还有表演要赶
All right, we got a show to catch.
希望我们没太晚
I hope we're not too late.
你没事吧？嗯
You all right? Yeah.
身份已验证
Identity verified.
你来了
You made it.
我要的东西带来了吗？
Do you have what I want?
如果你有我想要的
If you have what I want.
证据呢？
Where's the evidence?
就在这里
Right here.
我就是证据
I'm the evidence.
不
No.
查理，我……我不……
Charlie, I... I don't...
你死了
You're dead.
现在你看到我了
Now you see me.
人们为了让某些东西或某人消失
It's quite fascinating the things people do
而做的事情，真是令人着迷
to make something or someone...
消失
disappear.
啊
Ah.
那个戏法是我教你的
I taught you that trick.
就像我们的父亲教你一样
Just like our father taught you.
而现在，15年后，你……
And now, after 15 years, you're...
你想毁了我？
you're trying to ruin me?
不
No.
整整15年
All 15 years.
我不知道你当时在车里
I didn't know you'd be in that car.
但你听说我在时一定松了口气
But you must have been relieved to hear I was.
当我们冲进水里时，
When we hit the water,
我解不开安全带
I couldn't unbuckle my seat belt.
母亲用她最后一口气解开了我
Mom freed me with her dying breath.
查理，我曾经对你只有好感
I had nothing but fondness for you, Charlie.
让我最终像对待兄弟一样对待你
Let me finally treat you like a brother.
我就是你的兄弟！
I am your brother!
父亲的血液流淌在我们两人身上，
Father's blood is in both of us,
尽管他永远不会承认我
though he'd never acknowledge mine.
天知道母亲求过他多少次
God knows Mother begged.
而这份耻辱将我母亲送入了坟墓
And the shame drove my mother to her grave.
然后你又把我的母亲送进了她的坟墓！
Then you sent mine to hers!
好吧
Fine.
你是对的
You're right.
它应该属于你
It should be yours.
给
Here.
拿去吧
Take it.
徒手抓子弹
Bullet catch.
那不可能   不   只是魔术
That's impossible. No. Just magic.
啊
Ah.
嗯
Hmm.
大家好
Hello, everyone.
谢谢
Thank you.
好的，谢谢
All right, thank you.
今晚早些时候，J·丹尼尔·阿特拉斯
Earlier tonight, J. Daniel Atlas
承诺会将“心之钻”物归原主
promised to return the Heart Diamond to its rightful owner.
但在那之前，
But before we do that,
需要进行一些介绍
some introductions are in order.
首先，让我们欢迎这位充满力量的杰出人物，
First, let's say hello to the fierce force of nature,
非凡的琼·鲁克莱尔！
the extraordinary June Rouclere!
耶，琼！
Yeah, June!
哇   大家好   谢谢
Wow. Hello, everyone. Thank you.
非常感谢   谢谢
Thank you so much. Thank you.
再来欢迎这位不屈不挠的
And give it up for the indomitable.
博斯科·勒罗伊！
Bosco Leroy!
荣幸之至
The pleasure is ours.
你好，美女
Hello, gorgeous.
当然，若没有他们，我们根本不可能完成这一切
And, of course, we could not have done any of this in the first place
这一切，都离不开世界上最伟大的魔术师们的帮助
without the help of the world's greatest magicians.
四……
The Four...
抱歉，应该是五骑士！
Sorry, make that Five Horsemen!
谢谢大家
Thank you, everyone.
哇   呃……
Wow. Uh...
你知道，我们曾娱乐，嗯，
You know, we have entertained, well,
让世界各地的观众眼花缭乱，
dazzled audiences all over the world,
但我们从未参与过像这样的戏法
but we have never been part of a trick like this.
你们可能会问自己，
And you may be asking yourself,
“他们是怎么做到的？”
"How did they pull this off?"
好吧，每个魔术师都需要一个助手   维罗妮卡？
Okay, well, every magician needs an assistant. Veronika?
你们可能以为这里的维罗妮卡，
You may think Veronika here,
作为彼得·范德伯格的唯一继承人，
as Peter Vanderberg's sole heir,
是这颗钻石的合法主人
is the rightful owner of this diamond.
但是，这里有转折
But, here's the twist.
彼得不是只有一个孩子   他有两个
Peter didn't have one child. He had two.
没错
That's right.
而那个孩子侥幸逃生
And that other child cheated death.
然后落脚在纽约市
And landed in New York City.
在那里，复仇成为了他毕生的事业
Where vengeance became his life's work.
但他需要帮助
But he would need help.
哦   找到威士忌了   谢谢
Oh. Found the scotch. Thanks.
于是他招募
So he recruited.
什么时候停，告诉我
when to stop, tell me when.
停
Stop.
这是你的牌吗？是的
Is that your card? Yes.
是吗？想知道我怎么做到的吗？
Yeah? You want to know how I did it?
他吸引……
Enticed...
并网罗了一些他能召集到的
and lured some of the most
最具才华的头脑，
brilliant minds he could assemble,
为一场史无前例的戏法奠定了基础
laying the groundwork for a trick unlike any other.
这就引向了今晚
Which brings us to tonight.
让我们为这一切的幕后策划者欢呼吧
Make some noise for the mastermind behind all of this.
我们最好的朋友
Our best friend.
一个幽灵…… 直到此刻
A ghost... Until this very moment.
查理·范德伯格！
Charlie Vanderberg!
哇   哇！
Wow. Whoo!
我说过我会很享受把你扳倒，
I know I said I'd enjoy taking you down,
但这比我想象的更有趣
but this is more fun than I anticipated.
你仍然是个可悲又可怜的男人
You are still a sad and pathetic man.
而你什么都不是
And you are nothing.
哦，等一下，各位   稍等
Oh, hold on, everyone. One sec.
而且你永远不会是   那是什么？
And you never will be. What's that?
我不明白你是怎么做到的
I don't understand how you pulled this off.
你不明白？
You don't understand?
维罗妮卡似乎不明白
Veronika doesn't seem to understand
她怎么会落到这步田地
how she found herself in this position.
好吧，让我们向她解释一下
Well, let's explain it to her.
你看，最高明的魔术利用的是假设
You see, the finest magic preys on assumptions.
假设等着你的车
That the car waiting for you
就是送你来的那辆
was the same one that dropped you off.
我们走
Let's go.
假设一场自然现象仅仅就是自然现象
That an act of Mother Nature is nothing but.
假设沙漠里的一个金库
And that a vault in the desert
不只是烟雾和镜子
isn't just smoke and mirrors.
假设一把枪里装的不是空包弹
That a gun isn't filled with blanks.
假设一部电梯
And that an elevator
只是简单地下降入地
is just simply descending into earth.
如果你想骗过欺骗大师，
If you want to trick the master of deception,
你必须操控她的现实
you have to manipulate her reality.
而作为我们的最后一个魔术，
And for our last trick,
我们何不让维罗妮卡消失呢？
why don't we make Veronika disappear?
不
No.
你不会赢的
You don't win.
我是范德伯格家族！她在那儿
I'm the Vanderberg family! There she is.
已经想你了
Miss you already.
最终揭秘！你听到了吗？
Final reveal! Do you hear me?
真正的维罗妮卡·范德伯格
The real Veronika Vanderberg.
范德伯格家族不会输！
The Vanderbergs do not lose!
世界充满了假象
The world is full of illusions.
最大的假象之一，就是这颗钻石真的属于范德伯格家族
One of the biggest is that this diamond belongs to the Vanderbergs at all.
作为我父亲唯一未被监禁的直系亲属，
As my father's only unincarcerated next of kin,
我将确保我们每一位非法买家
I'll make sure every one of our illicit buyers
面临法律后果
faces legal repercussions.
然后我将捐赠我们所有的资产，
And then I'll gift all our assets,
包括“心之钻”，
including the Heart,
给它们来源地的南非社区，
to the South African communities they came from
并给你们所有人都留下一点额外的钱
with a few extra dollars left for all of you.
来看骑士表演的观众总会带着更鼓的钱包离开
Horsemen crowds always leave with deeper pockets.
好戏法   我师从最优秀的人
Nice trick. I learned from the best.
谢谢
Thank you.
感谢你们的参与，感谢所有人
Thank you for joining us, all of us.
请记住，
And please remember,
无论生活发给你什么牌，
no matter what cards life deals you,
你都要学会创造属于自己的魔术
you have to learn to make your own magic.
女士们先生们……
Ladies and gentlemen...
我们是骑士   晚安
We are the Horsemen. Good night.
好了，你想要什么口味的，
All right, what do you want,
石榴还是波森莓？
pomegranate or boysenberry?
伙计，我说了我想喝一杯
Dude, I said I wanted a drink.
就尝一口
Just give it a try.
现在的年轻人啊
Kids today.
嗯！当然
Mm! Of course.
味道不错
That's pretty good.
你想尝尝吗？不
You wanna try? No.
我想你掉了这个
I think you dropped this.
哦   我的旧名片
Oh. My old card.
万一你想裱起来呢
Just in case you wanna frame it.
谢谢   也许我会
Thanks. I might.
你知道吗，我还是不敢相信你是范德伯格家的人
You know, I still cannot believe you're a Vanderberg.
她也不敢相信
Neither could she.
我在想我觉得
I was thinking I feel like
我们应该成立自己的团体，姑娘们
we should start our own group, you guys.
一个女孩魔术团体？是啊，是啊，是啊
A girls magic group? Yeah, yeah, yeah.
是的   骑……骑马女孩
Yes. The Hor... Horsegirls.
不   不是那个   等等，骑马女侠
No. Not that. Wait, Horsewomen.
不是那个   马背淑女
Not that. Ladies of the Horse.
不会是那个   小马驹！
It wouldn't be that. Ponies!
那太糟糕了   是吗？
That's really bad. Yeah?
我能和你单独说句话吗？
Can I talk to you real quick?
哦！
Ooh!
我不是想打入骑马女侠内部
I'm not trying to infiltrate the Horsewomen.
什么……什么事？
What... what's up?
嗯……
Um...
只是……说吧
It's just... Speak.
你到底怎么了？出什么事了？
What is the matter with you? What's wrong?
这很难因为我不……
It's hard because I don't...
我不知道你的感受
I don't know how you feel.
所以……
And so...
嘿，呃，各位
Hey, uh, everybody.
各位，请过来一下
Everybody, come on over here, please.
嗯？来吧，伙计们
Yeah? Come on, guys.
嘿，你能再拿点那些美味的东西吗，博斯科？
Hey, can you grab some more of those delicious things, Bosco?
你们会爱上这玩意儿的   它超赞
You are gonna love this stuff. It is slap.
不，梅里特，别这样   它超赞
No, Merritt, please. It slaps.
我想说的是它很好喝
What I meant to say is it's good.
嗯   对
Yeah. Right.
是的，就由我来说吧
Yes, and I will be the one to say it.
我会想念你们的
I'm going to miss you guys.
我也正这么想
I was just thinking the same thing.
是啊   我也是
Yeah. Me, too.
该死，我爱你们
Damn it, I love you guys.
噢   我们也爱你
Aw. We love you, too.
我们爱你
We love you.
真可爱   我也是
Adorable. Me, too.
太温馨了   也包括我吗？
Very sweet. Even me?
真的吗？你一定是喝醉了
Really? You must be very drunk.
哇
Whoa.
哦，天哪   说点别的吧
Oh, my God. Just talk about something else.
回到刚才……我们都彼此相爱
Go back to what... We all love each other.
你爱他，他爱她   碰拳   碰拳
You love him, he loves her. Fist bump. Fist bump.
你们彼此更相爱
You guys love each other more.
哦
Oh.
你们在等人吗？
You guys expecting someone?
没人知道我们在哪
No one's supposed to know where we are.
谁寄来的？没写
Who's it from? Doesn't say.
打开看看
Open it.
你开
You open it.
好吧
Okay.
哦，那是……那是门上的那个东西
Oh, that's the... that's the thing from the door.
是啊，从城堡那拿的   哦，对！
Yeah, from the chateau. Oh, yeah!
你，呃……你介意我再试一次吗？
Do you, uh... You mind if I take another crack at it?
好啊，好啊，你来吧   真的？
Yeah, yeah, go for it. Yeah?
我想这次我能搞定
I think I can handle it this time.
你好，骑士们
Hello, Horsemen.
想我了吗？
Did you miss me?
迪伦
Dylan.
但他应该在监狱里
But he's supposed to be in prison.
我知道你们在想什么   “他骗了我们   ”
I know what you're thinking. "He lied to us."
但我……我没有骗你们
But I... I didn't lie to you.
我只是引导你们相信了不真实的事
I just led you to believe something that wasn't true.
但这是为你们好，相信我
But it was for your own good, trust me.
这个谜团比你们想象的更深
There's more to this mystery than you realize.
而最终的结果是
And the end result
骑士们又重聚了
is that the Horsemen are back together again.
这让我心里暖暖的
It warms my heart.
现在，对于你们三个冒牌货，
Now, for you three imposters,
厚颜无耻地假装
brazenly pretending like
你们是我们绝密组织的一部分？
you're part of our top secret organization?
你真以为干了这些事，自己能毫发无伤、全身而退？
You think you're gonna get away with it with no consequences or repercussions?
好吧……
Well...
你们想对了
you thought right.
嘿！欢迎
Hey! Welcome.
欢迎来到天眼
Welcome to The Eye.
至于你们其他人，
As for the rest of you,
你们以为工作结束了
you thought your work was done.
再想想吧，团队
Think again, team.
你们才刚刚开始
You're just getting started.
魔术是什么？
What's the trick?
快点
Hurry up
我发誓我真的没耐心了
I swear to God I'm out of patience
我来了
I pull up
不管有没有邀请
With or without an invitation
因为我如此耀眼 如此不凡
'Cause I'm so fly And I'm so money
宝贝 你可以看 但别碰
Baby, you can look But don't get touchy
我玩得很快 也玩得很狠
I go fast baby, I go hard
但我撞车时 不会留下一丝刮痕
But don't leave a scratch when I crash my car
在林荫大道上漫步于星辰
Steppin' on stars on the boulevard
我觉得这有点有趣
I find it kinda funny
我总是这么 啦-啦-啦-幸运
I get so la-la-la lucky
好吧 我自有办法
Okay, got my way
简直就像我是蕾妮
It's almost like I'm Renee
哦不 我去了哪？
Oh no, where'd I go?
现在你看见我 现在你看不见
Now you see me Now you don't
好吧 我自有办法
Okay, got my way
简直就像我是蕾妮
It's almost like I'm Renee
哦不 我去了哪
Oh no, where'd I go
现在你看见我 现在你看不见
Now you see me Now you don't
我玩得很快 也玩得很狠
I go fast baby, I go hard
但我撞车时 不会留下一丝刮痕
But don't leave a scratch when I crash my car
在林荫大道上漫步于星辰
Steppin' on stars on the boulevard
我觉得这有点有趣
I find it kinda funny
我总是这么 啦-啦-啦-幸运
I get so la-la-la lucky
啦-啦-啦-幸运
La-la-la-lucky
我觉得这有点有趣
I find it kinda funny
我总是这么 啦-啦-啦-幸运
I get so la-la-la lucky
啦-啦-啦-幸运
La-la-la-lucky
听我说完
Hear me out
我向来不太擅长倾听
I've never been too good at listenin'
但我擅长得到我想要的
I'm good at getting what I want
不需要宽恕 也不需要许可
Don't need forgiveness or permission
因为我如此耀眼 如此不凡
'Cause I'm so fly And I'm so money
宝贝 你可以看 但别碰
Baby, you can look But don't get touchy
我玩得很快 也玩得很狠
I go fast baby, I go hard
但我撞车时 不会留下一丝刮痕
But don't leave a scratch when I crash my car
在林荫大道上漫步于星辰
Steppin' on stars on the boulevard
我觉得这有点有趣
I find it kinda funny
我总是这么 啦-啦-啦-幸运
I get so la-la-la lucky
啦-啦-啦-幸运
La-la-la-lucky
我觉得这有点有趣
I find it kinda funny
我总是这么 啦-啦-啦-幸运
I get so la-la-la lucky